<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
  <addon id="metadata.album.universal"
       name="Universal Album Scraper"
       version="2.5.0"
       provider-name="Olympia, XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.0.2"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.8.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
               language="en"
               library="albumuniversal.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">Universele Skraper vir Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="ast">Scraper universal pa álbumes</summary>
      <summary lang="be">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за албуми</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per àlbums</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro alba</summary>
      <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Albymau Cyffredinol</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Universel Scraper til Albummer</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Universeller Scraper für Alben</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Άλμπουμ</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para álbumes</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Albumes</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal para Álbumes</summary>
      <summary lang="et">Universaalne albumite kraabits</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">Universaali tiedonhakija albumitiedoille</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper universel pour les Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les albums</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Scraper Universal para Álbums</summary>
      <summary lang="he">סקרייפר אוניברסלי עבור אלבומים</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija albuma</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Univerzális album leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Pengais Universal Album</summary>
      <summary lang="is">Universal Scraper fyrir Hljómplötur</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Ricercatore Universale per Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">汎用アルバムスクレーパー</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Universalus albumų skreperis</summary>
      <summary lang="lv">Albumu universālais skrāpis</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">Универзален превземач за Албуми</summary>
      <summary lang="ms">Pengikis Universel untuk Album</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Universele Scraper voor Albums</summary>
      <summary lang="no">Universalskraper for album</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Uniwersalny ekstraktor informacji o albumach muzycznych</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Colector universal para álbuns</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Álbuns</summary>
      <summary lang="ro"> Scraper universal pentru albume</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер для альбомов</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre albumy</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Univerzalni ponudnik informacij o albumih</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Universiell albumskrapa</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">ஆல்பங்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">Albümler için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">Універсальний здирач для альбомів</summary>
      <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu album từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">通用音乐专辑信息刮削器</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">通用音樂專輯訊息搜刮器</summary>
      <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper kollekteer inligting vanaf die volgende ondersteunde werwe: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de, terwyl kunswerke gegryp word vanaf: fanart.tv, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifieke inligting wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvaklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval skakels van allmusic en/of amazon.de nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde vanaf allmusic.com en/of amazon.de nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
      <description lang="ast">Esti scraper recueye información de les siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mentanto obtién les imáxenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quier obtener la información pa cada campu. ⏎ ⏎ La gueta inicial faise siempre en MusicBrainz. En casu de que los enllaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de nun tean amestaos na web de MusicBrainz, nun van poder obtenese los campos d'información d' estos dos sitios (magar que ye mui fácil amestar esos enllaces que falten)</description>
      <description lang="be">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не са налични препратки към allmusic и/или amazon.de на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com и/или amazon.de става невъзможно (добавянето им е много лесно).</description>
      <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, alhora que agafa art de: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Es pot configurar camp a camp des de quin lloc voleu aquella informació específica. &#10;&#10;La cerca inicial es realitza sempre a MusicBrainz. En el cas que els enllaços d'allmusic i amazon.de no s'afegeixin al lloc MusicBrainz els camps d'allmusic i amazon.de i/o amazon.com no es poden obtenir (tot i que són fàcils d'afegir aquests enllaços restants).</description>
      <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj získává data z následujících podporovaných stránek: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možno podrobně nastavit, které informace si přejete získat ze kterých stránek.&#10;&#10;Prvotní vyhledání je vžy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že odkaz pro allmusic a nebo amazon.de není přidaný na stránku MusicBrainz, není možné údaje z allmusic.com a amazon.de stáhnout (avšak je velmi snadné tyto chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
      <description lang="cy">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ac amazon.de, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny)</description>
      <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, hvilke sider du ønsker, at få den pågældende information fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic og/eller amazon.de linkene er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
      <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com και amazon.de, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic ή/και το amazon.de στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com ή/και το amazon.de (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
      <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="en_NZ">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="es">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic y/o amazon.de no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com y/o amazon.de no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
      <description lang="et">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de, pilte: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic ja/või amazon.de linke lisatud, siis neilt lehtedelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
      <description lang="fi">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja:MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic- ja/tai amazon.de-linkkejä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
      <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur utilise les informations des sites suivant : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de et télécharge les artwork depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez spécifier quel site utiliser pour récupérer chaque information.&#10;&#10;Le premier résultat est toujours en provenance de MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site MusicBrainz, les champs de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être traités (il est toutefois très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este scraper obtén a información dende os seguintes sitios: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentres que as ilustracións as obtén dende: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pódese definir dende que sitios se obterá a información específica de cada campo.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial faise sempre en MusicBrainz. No caso de non estar engadidas as ligazón de allmusic e/ou amazon.de no sitio de MusicBrainz, os campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de non se poderán obter (aínda que é moi doado engadir as ligazóns).</description>
      <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
      <description lang="hr">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.&#10;&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic i/ili amazon.de poveznice nisu dodane na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com i/ili amazon.de ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
      <description lang="hu">A leolvasó szöveges infókat gyűjt a támogatott oldalakról: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, valamint képeket a : fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com-ról. Beállítható hogy honnan, és milyen infót gyűjtsön. A keresés mindig a MusicBrainz-on folyik, de könnyen hozzáadhatjuk a hiányzó találatokat az allmusic.com, vagy az amazon.de-ről.</description>
      <description lang="id">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, lastfm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
      <description lang="is">Þessi skafa nær í upplýsingar frá eftirfarandi stöðum sem eru studdir: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, og nær í myndefni frá: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic og/eða amazon.de tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com og/eða amazon.de (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
      <description lang="it">Questo ricercatore prende informazioni dai seguenti siti: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentre prende grafica da: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Puoi impostare campo per campo cosa prendere e da dove.⏎ ⏎La ricerca iniziale viene sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. In caso i links a allmusic e/o amazon.de non sono stati messi su MusicBrainz, i campi da questi siti non possono essere recuperati (è molto facile aggiungere quei link, comunque).</description>
      <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic や amazon.de のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com / amazon.de からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
      <description lang="ko">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de. 아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="lt">Šis skreperis surenka informaciją iš šių palaikomų puslapių: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ir amazon.de bei atsiunčia iliustracijas iš: fanart.tv, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatytas laukas po laiko, kad nurodyti iš kokio puslapio paimti konkrečią informaciją.&#10;&#10;Pradinė paieška visada atliekama MusicBrainz puslapyje. Jei kartais allmusic ir/raba amazon.de nuorodos nepridėtos į MusicBrainz puslapį, laukai iš allmusic.com ir/arba amazon.de negalės būti gauti (tačiau labai lengva pridėti tas trūkstamas nuorodas).</description>
      <description lang="mk">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.⏎ ⏎ The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="ms">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com dan amazon.de, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de sukar didapati.</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde sites: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de. Afbeeldingen worden verzameld van de volgende sites: fanart.tv, Last.fm en allmusic.com. Per veld kan aangegeven worden van welke site je de specifieke informatie wil halen. De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd gedaan van MusicBrainz.&#10;&#10;In het geval dat links naar allmusic en/of amazon.de niet zijn toegevoegd op de MusicBrainz site, kunnen velden niet worden opgehaald bij deze sites. (Het is niet moeilijk om de ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
      <description lang="no">Denne skraperen innsamler informasjon fra følgende nettsteder: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, mens den henter grafikk fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan selv bestemme hvilken kilde du ønsker å hente informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket blir alltid gjort med MusicBrainz. Hvis allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de linker ikke tilgjengelig hos MusicBrainz, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de hentes (dog er det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
      <description lang="pl">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących stron: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com oraz amazon.de, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane na MusicBrainz. Gdy linki do allmusic i/lub amazon.de nie są dodane na stronie MusicBrainz, nie można pobrać tych pól z allmusic.com i/lub amazon.de (pomimo to brakujące linki można bardzo łatwo dodać).</description>
      <description lang="pt">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio do qual quer obter as informações. A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso os endereços allmusic e/ou amazon.de não tenham sido adicionados no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta). </description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
      <description lang="ro">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com și amazon.de. Elementele de grafica sunt accesate din: fanart.tv, last.fm și allmusic.com. Acesta poate fi setat câmp cu câmp pentru ca informatiile colectate sa fie cele dorite.⏎ &#10;⏎ &#10;Căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna pe MusicBrainz. În cazul în care Allmusic și/sau link-ul amazon.de nu sunt adăugate pe MusicBrainz, câmpurile din allmusic.com și/sau amazon.de nu pot fi colectate (este foarte ușor însă de adăugat aceste legături lipsă).</description>
      <description lang="ru">Данный скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de, при этом получая обложки из: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле можно настроить так, чтобы оно получало желаемую информацию с определенного вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Начальный поиск всегда проводится на  MusicBrainz. Для allmusic и/или amazon.de ссылки на сайт MusicBrainz отсутствуют, поля с allmusic.com и/или amazon.de не могут быть заполнены (добавить пропущенные ссылки очень просто).</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera informácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com a amazon.de, zatiaľ čo umeleckú grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic a/alebo amazon.de nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com a/alebo amazon.de (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
      <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com in amazon.de; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com in/ali amazon.de, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
      <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com och amazon.de, och konstverk från: fanart.tv, last.fm och allmusic.com. Det kan anges fält för fält vilken sajt du vill få den specifika informationen.⏎ ⏎ Den initiala sökningen är alltid utförd på MusicBrainz sajt, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de länkarna läggs inte till på MusicBrainz sajten, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de kan inte hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com மற்றும் amazon.de ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
      <description lang="tr">Bu scraper bilgileri toplamak için şu siteleri desteklemektedir:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ve amazon.de, çizimleri için ise: fanart.tv, last.fm ve allmusic.com desteklenmektedir. Her bilginin özellikle nereden alınacağını tek tek ayarlayabilirsiniz.&#10;&#10;İlk olarak arama daima MusicBrainz'de yapılır. MusicBrainz'e allmusic ve/veya amazon.de linkleri eklenmemiş olması durumunda allmusic.com'dan ve/veya amazon.de'den ilgili alanlar alınamaz (gerçi bu eksik linkleri eklemek çok kolaydır).</description>
      <description lang="uk">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com та amazon.de, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, last.fm та allmusic.com.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic і/або amazon.de не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com і/або amazon.de неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
      <description lang="vi">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic và/hoặc amazon.de không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com và/hoặc amazon.de sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
      <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com 和 amazon.de，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取。如果 MusicBrainz 网站没有到 allmusic 和/或 amazon.de 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的/或 amazon.de 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
      <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com和amazon.de，並從以下網站取得專輯照片：fanart.tv、last.fm和allmusic.com。您並可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得。如果MusicBrainz網站沒有加入到allmusic和/或amazon.de的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的/或amazon.de的信息(當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL v2.0</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=133547</forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.artists.universal"
       name="Universal Artist Scraper"
       version="3.6.1"
       provider-name="Olympia, XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.3.2"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.0.2"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.8.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
               language="en"
               library="artistuniversal.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">Universal Skraper vir Kunstenaars</summary>
      <summary lang="ar">ماسحة الفنان العالمية</summary>
      <summary lang="be">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за артисти</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per artistes</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro umělce</summary>
      <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Cyffredinol ar gyfer Artistiaid</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Universel Scraper til Kunstnere</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Universeller Scraper für Interpreten</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Καλλιτεχνών</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal de Artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="et">Universaalne artistide kraabits</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">Universaali artistien tiedonhakija</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Collecteur universel d'artistes</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les artistes</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="he">Universa סקרייפר אמנים</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija izvođača</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Univerzális előadó leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Pengais Universal untuk Artis</summary>
      <summary lang="is">Almenn skafa fyrir Listamenn</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Scraper universale degli artisti</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">汎用アーティストスクレーパー</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Universalus Artistų Scrapers</summary>
      <summary lang="lv">Mākslinieku universālais skrāpis</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
      <summary lang="ms">Pengikis Universal untuk Artis</summary>
      <summary lang="my">အနုပညာရှင်များအတွက် Universal Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Universele scraper voor artiesten</summary>
      <summary lang="no">Universalskraper for artister</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Universal Scraper informacji o artystach muzycznych</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Colector universal para Artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Scraper universal pentru artisti</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер для исполнителей</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre umelcov</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Univerzalen ponudnik informacij o izvajalcih</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Universiell artistskrapa</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">கலைஞர்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">Sanatçılar için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">Універсальний здирач для виконавців</summary>
      <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu Nghệ sĩ từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">通用艺术家信息刮削器</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">通用演出者訊息搜括器</summary>
      <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper versamel informasie van die volgende ondersteunde werwe: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com, terwyl kunswerke gryp van: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifike informasie wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvanklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval die allmusic skakel nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde van allmusic.com nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
      <description lang="ar">هذه الماسحة تجمع المعلومات من المواقع المدعومة التالية: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, في حين تأخذ عناوين الأعمال الفنية من: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. يمكن أن ترتب حقل تلو حقل حسب الموقع الذي تريد منه تلك المعلومة المحددة.&#10;&#10;البحث الابتدائي يتم دائما على ميوزك برينز. في حال أن رابط كل الموسيقى غير مضاف على حقول موقع ميوزك برينز من allmusic.com لا يمكن الحصول عليها(على الرغم من سهولة إضافة هذه الروابط المفقودة).</description>
      <description lang="be">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не е налична препратка към allmusic.com на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com става невъзможно (добавянето на препратка е много лесно).</description>
      <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs suportats</description>
      <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj dat získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Lze nastavit jakou informaci stahovat z jakých stránek.&#10;&#10;Základní hledání je vždy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že schází odkaz allmusic na stránce MusicBrains, nelze stáhnout informace z allmusic.com (avšak je velmi snadné chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
      <description lang="cy">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, a allmusic.com, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny).</description>
      <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, fra hvilke sider du ønsker, at få de pågældende informationer fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic linket er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
      <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm και allmusic.com, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
      <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="es">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras que obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
      <description lang="et">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm ja allmusic.com, pilte: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic  linki lisatud, siis allmusic.com lehelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
      <description lang="fi">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic-linkkiä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle allmusic.com-osoitteessa, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
      <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur répertorie les informations des sites suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, Last.fm et allmusic.com tout en assemblant les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez définir la source d'information pour chaque champ.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite à partir de MusicBrainz. xxxxxxxx (en attente du retour de l'équipe Kodi) xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm et allmusic.com, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este scraper recolle información dos seguintes sitios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, mentres que, obtén as imaxes de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir en cada campo o sitio de onde quere obter a información.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial é feita sempre no MusicBrainz, no caso de que a ligazón a allmusic non se teña engadido nos campos do sítio MusicBrainz dende allmusic.com, non se poderán obter (aínda que, é moi doado engadir as ligazóns que faltan).</description>
      <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
      <description lang="hr">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm i allmusic.com, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.\n&#10;\n&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic poveznica nije dodana na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
      <description lang="hu">Ez a leolvasó a következő weboldalakról gyűjti be az adatokat:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm és allmusic.com, míg képeket a következő oldalakról gyűjt: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm és allmusic.com. Egyenként beállítható, hogy az adott mezőt melyik weboldalról töltse fel⏎ ⏎ A kiinduló keresés mindig a MusicBrainz. Amennyiben az allmusic utalás nincs hozzáadva MusicBrainz oldalhoz, a mezők nem tölthetők le az allmusic.com oldalról (a hiányzó utalások hozzáadása azonban nagyon egyszerű).</description>
      <description lang="id">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com. last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic belum ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
      <description lang="is">Þessi skafa safnar sama upplýsingum frá eftirfarandi studdum stöðum: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og á meðan nær hún í myndir frá: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
      <description lang="it">Lo scraper colleziona informazioni da questi siti supportati: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, e allmusic.com, mentre ottiene le grafiche da: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Può essere impostato campo per campo da quale sito vuoi la specifica informazione.&#10;&#10;La ricerca iniziale è sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. Nel caso che il link allmusic non è stato aggiunto al campo del sito MusicBrainz da allmusic.com; non possono essere ottenute (è comunque veramente facile aggiungere questi link mancanti).</description>
      <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
      <description lang="ko">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com.아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다.&#10;&#10;초기 검색은 항상 MusicBrainz에서 수행합니다. allmusic 링크가 MusicBrainz 사이트의 필드에 추가되어 있지 않은 경우 정보를 가져올 수 없습니다(누락된 링크는 쉽게 추가할 수 있습니다).</description>
      <description lang="lt">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, ir allmusic.com, ir atsiunčia meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatyti lauko srityje, kurioje svetainėje norite, kad konkrečiu atveju pradinė informacijos pradinis paieška visada bus atlikta remiantis MusicBrainz. Allmusic nuoroda įdėta į MusicBrainz vietoje laukų allmusic.com negali būti (nors tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva įtraukti).</description>
      <description lang="mk">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
      <description lang="ms">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, htbckdrops.com, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com sukar didapati.</description>
      <description lang="my">ဒီ Scraper သည် အချက်အလက်များကို အောက်ဖော်ပြပါ ထောက်ပံ့ထားသော ဆိုဒ်များမှ စုဆောင်းပါသည်။ ထိုဆိုဒ်များမှာ TheAudioDb.com,MusicBrainz,last..fm, နှင့် allmusic.com တို့ဖြစ်သည်။</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde websites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com en tevens pakt hij afbeeldingen van fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Het is mogelijk om per veld aan te geven van welke website je de specifieke informatie wilt halen.&#10;&#10;De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd uitgevoerd op MusicBrainz. Wanneer de allmusic link niet is toegevoegd in de juiste velden op de MusicBrainz website kan de informatie van allmusic.com niet worden opgehaald. (Het is erg makkelijk om deze ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
      <description lang="no">Denne skraperen samler informasjon fra følgende støttede steder: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm og allmusic.com, mens den henter artwork fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan stegvis velge hvilken kilde du ønsker og hente spesifikk informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket er alltid gjort hos MusicBrainz. I tilfeller hvor allmusic-linker ikke er lagt til hos MusicBrainz-siden, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com hentes (det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
      <description lang="pl">Ten ekstraktor pobiera informacje z następujących stron: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane w serwisie MusicBrainz. Gdy wyszukiwanie nie jest wskazane na stronę MusicBrainz, następuje przeszukiwanie serwisu allmusic.com (brakujące linki można łatwo dodać później).</description>
      <description lang="pt">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio de onde quer obter as informações. &#10;&#10;A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso um endereço allmusic não tenha sido adicionado no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta).</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
      <description lang="ro">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, și allmusic.com, și opere de artă de la: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm și allmusic.com. Poate fi setat câmp cu câmp de pe care site-ul doriți informații specifice ⏎ ⏎ căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna face pe MusicBrainz.. În cazul în care link-ul Allmusic nu este adăugat la MusicBrainz, allmusic.com nu poate fi folosit (însă este relativ ușor să adăugați aceste link-uri lipsă).</description>
      <description lang="ru">Этот скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm и allmusic.com, при этом получая обложки с: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле может быть настроено для получения определенной информации с желаемого вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Первичный поиск всегда производится на MusicBrainz. Если линк для allmusic не добавлен на сайте MusicBrainz, то поля с allmusic.com не могут быть заполнены (добавить отсутствующие ссылки очень легко).</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera infomácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm a allmusic.com. Grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
      <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm in allmusic.com; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
      <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm och allmusic.com, medans den samlar konstverk från: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm och allmusic.com. Du kan ange fält för fält från vilken sajt du vill ha den specifika inforamtionen från. Den initiala sökningen är alltid gjord på MusicBrainz. Om inte allmusic.com länken läggs till på MusicBrainz sajten, kan inte fält från allmusic.com hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
      <description lang="uk">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm та allmusic.com, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm та allmusic.com. Для кожного поля можно вказати з якої сторінки ви бажаєте його заповнити.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
      <description lang="vi">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
      <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm 和 allmusic.com，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取，如果 MusicBrainz 网站未加入到 allmusic 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
      <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm和allmusic.com，並從以下網站取得專輯圖片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm和allmusic.com。您可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得，如果MusicBrainz網站未加入到allmusic的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的資訊 (當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL v2.0</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=132623</forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.tvdb.com"
       name="The TVDB"
       version="1.8.2"
       provider-name="XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.7.8"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.tvshows"
               language="multi"
               library="tvdb.xml"
               cachepersistence="00:15"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">Gaan haal TV vertoning metadata vanaf TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="be">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Изтегля информация за ТВ Сериали от TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Obté les metadades de les sèries de televisió de TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Získat metadata televizního pořadu z TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="cy">Estyn metadata sioeau Teledu o TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Hent metadata til TV-serier fra TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Lade TV-Show-Metadaten von TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Λήψη μετα-δεδομένων σειρών από το TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="en_NZ">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="en_US">Fetch TV show metadata from TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Recuperar metadatos de series de TV en TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Recuperar metadatos de series de TV en TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Obtener metadata de Series desde TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="et">Hangi tv seriaalide metainfo TheTVDB.com-ist</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">Nouda TV-ohjelmien tietoja TheTVDB.com -sivustolta</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Collecter les métadonnées des séries TV depuis TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Récupérer les métadonnées pour les séries télé depuis TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Obter os metadatos das series de TV dende TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="he">הבא מידע </summary>
      <summary lang="hi">द टी भी दी बी.कॉम से टी वी प्रदर्शन लाए</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Nabavi informacije za TV serije s TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">TV műsor információk a TheTVDB.com-ról</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Ambil metadata Serial TV dari TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="is">Sækja Sjónvarpsþátta lýsigögn frá TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Scarica informazioni programma TV da TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">TheTVDB.com からTV番組メタデータを取得</summary>
      <summary lang="ka">სატელევიზიო გადაცემების მეტაინფორმაციის გადმოტანა TVDB.com-დან</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">TheTVDB.com 에서 TV 쇼 정보 가져오기</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Parsiųsti TV šou (serialo) metaduomenis iš TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">Превземи ТВ шоу метаподаток од TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ms">Dapatkan data meta rancangan TV dari TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="my">TV show နှင့်ပတ်သက်သည့် အချက်အလက်များကို TheTVDB.com မှ ရယူရန်</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Seriemetadata ophalen van TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="no">Hent TV program data fra TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Pobieraj dane o serialach telewizyjnych z TheTVDB.com </summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Obtenha metadados para séries TV a partir de TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Obtenha dados dos seriados do TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Obţineţi datele despre seriale de la TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Загрузка информации о ТВ-шоу с TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TV-seriemetadata från TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Získať metadáta o televíznej relácii zo stránky TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Prenesite informacije o TV serijah z TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sq">Merr "metadata" mbi TV serialet nga TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Hämta TV-seriemetadata från TVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">TheTVDB.com இருந்து தொலைக்காட்சி நிகழ்ச்சி மெட்டாடேட்டா எடுக்கபடுகின்றது</summary>
      <summary lang="th">เรียกข้อมูลหลักของรายการทีวี จาก TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">TV programı meta verilerini TheTVDB.com'dan al</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">Отримання відомостей про серіали із TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy TV show từ TheTVDB.com</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">从 TheTVDB.com 获取电视剧集信息</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">從 TheTVDB.com 取得電視節目資訊</summary>
      <description lang="af">TheTVDB.com is 'n TV Skraper. Die werf is 'n massiewe oop databasis wat deur enige iemand verander kan word en bevat vol meta data vir baie vertonings in verskillende tale. Alle inhoud en prente op die werf is bygedra deur sy gebruikers vir sy gebruikers en het 'n hoë standaard van kwaliteit. Die databasis skema en webruimte is oopbron onder die GPL.</description>
      <description lang="be">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
      <description lang="bg">TheTVDB.com предоставя информация за ТВ Сериали. Сайтът е масивна отворена база данни, която може да бъде променяна от всеки и съдържа пълни мета данни за много сериали на различни езици. Цялото съдържание и изображенията в сайта са предоставени от неговите потребители за други потребители и имат високо ниво на качество. Структурата на базата данни и уеб сайта са създадени с отворен код под GPL лиценз.</description>
      <description lang="ca">TheTVDB.com és un raspador de TV. El lloc és una base de dades oberta massiva que pot ser modificat per qualsevol persona i conté metadades completes de molts programes en diferents idiomes. Tot el contingut i imatges en el lloc han estat aportat pels usuaris per als usuaris i tenen un alt nivell o qualitat. L'esquema de la base de dades i la pàgina web són de codi obert sota la llicència GPL.</description>
      <description lang="cs">TheTVDB.com je zdroj metadat pro televizní pořady. Stránka je masivní otevřená databáze, kterou může kdokoliv upravovat a obsahuje veškerá metadata v různých jazycích k mnoha pořadům. Všechen obsah a obrázky jsou poskytnuty uživateli pro uživatele a mají vysokou kvalitu. Návrhový vzor databáze a webová stránka jsou svobodný software licencovaný pod GPL.</description>
      <description lang="cy">Mae TheTVDB.com yn Grafwr Teledu. Mae'r wefan yn gronfa ddata anferthol agored y mae modd ei addasu gan unrhyw un  ac yn cynnwys meta data llaw llawer o sioeau mewn ieithoedd gwahanol. Mae'r holl gynnwys a delweddau ar y wefan wedi ei gyfrannu gan eu defnyddwyr ac i safon uchel . Mae cynllun y gronfa ddata a'r wefan yn god agored o dan y GPL.</description>
      <description lang="da">TheTVDB.com er en TV-scraper. Siden er en massiv åben database, som alle kan modificere, og den indeholder fyldestgørende metadata for mange serier på forskellige sprog. Alt indhold og alle billeder på siden er tilføjet af brugere og har en høj standard eller kvalitet. Databasens model og webside er open source under GPL.</description>
      <description lang="de">TheTVDB.com ist ein Scraper für TV-Shows. Die Seite ist eine riesige, offene Datenbank, die von jedem angepasst werden kann und weitreichende Metadaten für viele TV-Shows, in verschiedenen Sprachen, enthält. Alle Inhalte und Bilder dieser Seite wurden von Benutzern für Benutzer zusammengetragen und folgen dabei dem hohen Standard für Qualität. Das Datenbankschema sowie die Webseite sind nach der GPL-Lizenvereinbarung OpenSource.</description>
      <description lang="el">Το TVDB.com είναι ένα Scraper Τηλεόρασης. Η ιστοσελίδα είναι μία τεράστια ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων η οποία μπορεί να τροποποιηθεί από τον καθένα και περιέχει πλήρη μετα-δεδομένα για πολλές σειρές σε διάφορες γλώσσες. Όλο το περιεχόμενο και οι εικόνες στην ιστοσελίδα προέρχονται από τους χρήστες του, και έχουν υψηλά πρότυπα ποιότητας. Το σχήμα της βάσης δεδομένων και της ιστοσελίδας είναι ανοικτού κώδικα υπό το GPL.</description>
      <description lang="en">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
      <description lang="en_NZ">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
      <description lang="en_US">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
      <description lang="es">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de TV. El sitio es una enorme base de datos abierta que puede ser modificada por cualquiera y que contiene metadatos completos de muchas series en diferentes idiomas. Todos los contenidos e imágenes del sitio han sido aportados por sus usuarios y tienen una alta calidad. El esquema de base de datos y sitio web son de código abierto bajo la licencia GPL.</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de TV. El sitio es una enorme base de datos abierta que puede ser modificada por cualquiera y que contiene metadatos completos de muchas series en diferentes idiomas. Todos los contenidos e imágenes del sitio han sido aportados por sus usuarios y tienen una alta calidad. El esquema de base de datos y sitio web son de código abierto bajo la licencia GPL.</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">TheTVDB.com es un scraper de series de TV. Este sitio es una base de datos masiva y abierta que puede ser modicada por cualquiera y contiene metadata completa para muchas series en diferentes lenguajes. Todo el contenido e imágenes del sitio han sido contribuidos por sus usuarios para usuarios, los cuales tienen un alto estándar de calidad. El esquema de la base de datos y el sitio web son de código abierto bajo GPL.</description>
      <description lang="et">TheTVDB.com on seriaalide kraabits. See leht on mahukas avatud andmebaas mida saavad täiendad kõik ja sisaldab palju metaandmeid suure hulga seriaalide kohta. Kõik sisu ja pildid lehel on kasutajate poolt sisestatud ning vastavad kõrgele kvaliteedile. TheTVDB.com andmebaasi struktuur ja kood on avaldatud GPLi all.</description>
      <description lang="fi">TheTVDB.com on TV-ohjelmatietojen lataaja. Sivusto on massiivinen avoin tietokanta, jonka tietoja kaikki pystyy muokkaamaan ja se sisältää täydet tiedot monista TV-ohjelmista usealla eri kielellä. Kaikki sivuston sisältö ja kuvat on korkealaatuisia ja käyttäjien lahjoittamia. Tietokanta ja sivusto ovat GPL-lisenssin alaisia.</description>
      <description lang="fr">TheTVDB.com est un collecteur TV. Le site est une immense base de données libre pouvant être modifiée par tout le monde et contenant toutes les informations de nombreuses séries en différentes langues. Les informations et images du site proviennent de contributions d'utilisateurs pour les usagers et sont d'excellentes qualités. Le schéma de la base de données et le site Web sont en open source sous licence GPL.</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">TheTVDB est un extracteur pour séries télé. Ce site est une énorme base de données ouverte qui peut être modifiée par n'importe qui et qui comprend des métadonnées complètes pour beaucoup de séries télé dans plusieurs langues. Tout le contenu et les images présentes sur le site ont été fournis par les utilisateurs et possèdent un haut niveau de qualité. La structure de la base de données et le site Web sont libres et sous licence GPL.</description>
      <description lang="gl">TheTVDB.com é un Scraper de TV. O sitio é unha enorme base de datos aberta que calquera pode modificar e contén todos os metadatos de centos de series en diferentes idiomas. Todo o contido e imaxes do sitio foi proporcionado polos seus usuarios e amosa un grande estándar de calidade. O esquema da base de datos e o sitio web son de código aberto baixo licenza GPL.</description>
      <description lang="he">TheTVDB.com הוא סקרייפר עבור תוכניות טלוויזיה. אתר זה הוא מסד נתונים פתוח עצום אשר כל אחד יכול לערוך ומכיל פרטים מלאים להרבה תוכניות טלוויזיה בשפות שונות. כל התכנים והתמונות באתר נתרמו ע"י המשתמשים שלה עבור משתמשים וישנו סטנדרט גבוה או איכות גבוהה. תכנית המסד נתונית והאתר הם בקוד פתוח תחת ה-GPL.</description>
      <description lang="hi">टीभीडीबी एक टीभी स्क्रॅपर है.येह साइट एक बहुत बरा खुला डेटाबेस है जो किसी से भी रूपांतर्न किया जा सकता है और यह ह्र भासाओ मे सभी प्रदर्शन के लिए मीटा दाता रखता है.सभी सामग्री और चित्र यूज़र के लिए यूज़र का योगदान है और उच्च मानक या गुणवत्ता रखता है.डेटाबेस स्कीम और वेबसाइट जीपील् की अंतर्गत ओपन सोर्स है.</description>
      <description lang="hr">TheTVDB.com je sakupljač informacija za TV programe. Stranica je ogromna otvorena baza podataka koju može bilo tko mijenjati i sadrži mnogo informacija za različite serije na različitim jezicima. Sav sadržaj i slike postavili su korisnici za ostale korisnike i visoke su kvalitete. Shema baze podataka i web stranice su otvorenog kôda pod GPL licencom.</description>
      <description lang="hu">A TheTVDB.com egy TV műsor leolvasó. Az oldal egy hatalmas adatbázis amit bárki szabadon módosíthat és rengeteg TV műsor adatait tartalmazza különböző nyelveken. A minőségi tartalom és képanyag ezen az oldalon felhasználóktól származik más felhasználók számára. Az adatbázisstruktúra és a weblap nyílt forráskódú a GPL licenc alatt.</description>
      <description lang="id">TheTVDB.com adalah pengais Serial TV. Situs ini adalah database yang sangat besar dan terbuka yang dapat dimodifikasi oleh semua orang dan mengandung meta data yang penuh untuk banyak Serial TV di bahasa yang berbeda. Semua konten dan gambar dalam situ ini dikontribusikan oleh penggunanay untuk pengguna dan memiliki standar dan kualitas tinggi. Skema database dan situs adalah open-source dengan lisensi GPL.</description>
      <description lang="is">TheTVDB.com er sjónvarpsskafa.. Þessi veita er risastór opinn gagnagrunnur sem allir geta breytt og er með öll lýsigögn fyrir fullt af þáttum á mörgum tungumálum. Allt efni og myndir á veitunni er sett inn af notendum fyrir notendur og eru í háum staðli eða gæðum. Uppsetning gagnagrunnsins og vefsíðan eru 'open source under the GPL'</description>
      <description lang="it">TheTVDB.com è uno scraper di programmi TV. Questo sito è un enorme database che può essere modificato da chiunque, e contiene tutte le informazioni di molti show in varie lingue. Tutti i contenuti e le immagini sul sito sono stati forniti dagli utenti, ed hanno un alto standard di qualità. Lo schema del database e il sito internet sono open source sotto licenza GPL.</description>
      <description lang="ja">TheTVDB.com は TV スクレーパーです。本サイトは強力でオープンなデータベースで、誰もが追加修正可能です。テレビ番組のメタデータは多くの言語で提供されています。番組情報や画像データはユーザにより提供され、そのクオリティは非常に高いものです。データベーススキーマと web サイトは GPL ライセンスのオープンソースです。</description>
      <description lang="ko">TheTVDB.com 은 TV 정보수집기입니다. 위 사이트는 이용자가 직접 수정할 수 있으며 다양한 언어의 완전한 메타 데이터를 포함하는 방대한 오픈 데이터베이스입니다. 사이트의 모든 콘텐츠와 이미지들은 사이트 이용자들이 다른 이용자들을 위해 제공한 것이며 높은 품질을 가지고 있습니다. 웹사이트와 데이터베이스 스키마는 GLP 오픈소스입니다.</description>
      <description lang="lt">TheTVDB.com yra TV Scraper. Ši svetainė yra didžiulė atvira duomenų bazė, kuria gali pakeisti bet kas ir kurioje visa meta duomenis bazė daugelo šou įvairiomis kalbomis. Visas svetainės turinys atnaujinamas/papyldomasvartotojų ir turi aukštą kokybės standartą. Duomenų bazės ir svetainės yra atviro kodo pagal GPL standartą.</description>
      <description lang="mk">TheTVDB.com is a TV Scraper. The site is a massive open database that can be modified by anybody and contains full meta data for many shows in different languages. All content and images on the site have been contributed by their users for users and have a high standard or quality. The database schema and website are open source under the GPL.</description>
      <description lang="ms">TheTVDB.com adalah Pengikis TV. Laman tersebut merupakan pangkalan data terbuka yang amat besar dan boleh diubahsuai oleh sesiapa pun dan juga mengandungi data meta pelbagai rancangan  dalam pelbagai bahasa. Semua kandungan dan imej di laman ini disumbang oleh pengguna mereka untuk pengguna mereka dan mempunyai piawaian dan kualiti yang amat tinggi. Skema pangkalan data dan laman adalah sumber terbuka dibawah GPL.</description>
      <description lang="my">TheTVDB.com သည် TV Scraper ဖြစ်သည်။ database ထဲတွင် အချက်အလက်များစွာရှိနေပြီး မည်သူမဆို မည်သည့် ဘာသာစကားနှင့် မဆို ဝင်ရောက်ပြုပြင် နိုင်သည်။ အချက်အလက်များနှင့် ပုံများသည် ၎င်းတို့၏ အသုံးပြုသူများမှ အခြားအသုံးပြုသူများအတွက် ပံ့ပိုးထားသော အဆင်မြင့် အရေအသွေးများဖြစ်သည်။ website နှင့် database သည် open source GPL လိုင်စင် ကို အသုံးပြုထားသည်။</description>
      <description lang="nl">TheTVDB.com is een seriescraper. De site is een gigantische open databank die iedereen kan aanpassen en uitbreiden, en biedt metadata aan voor TV-series in verschillende talen. Alle inhoud en afbeeldingen zijn afkomstig van gebruikers en moeten een grondige kwaliteitscontrole doorstaan. Het databankschema en de websitecode zijn vrijgegeven onder de open source GPL-licentie.</description>
      <description lang="no">TheTVDB.com er en Tv Skraper. Siden er en massiv åpen database som kan endres av alle og inneholder data for mange forskjellige programmer på mange språk. Alt innholdet og bildene på siden er lagt til av brukere for brukere og har høy standard og kvalitet. Database skjemaet og websiden er åpen kildekode underlagt GPL.</description>
      <description lang="pl">TheTVDB.com jest ekstraktorem informacji o serialach telewizyjnych. Serwis jest ogromną, wielojęzykową i otwartą bazą danych o serialach, którą może edytować każdy. Zawartość tego serwisu została stworzona przez użytkowników, dla użytkowników. Dostępne materiały są najwyższej jakości.</description>
      <description lang="pt">O TheTVDB.com é um colector para séries TV. O site é uma gigantesca base de dados livre que pode ser alterada por qualquer pessoa e contém informação em várias línguas. Todos os conteúdos do site foram enviados por utilizadores e têm um elevado padrão de qualidade. A base de dados e o site funcionam sob uma licença GPL de software livre.</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">TheTVDB.com é um scraper de seriados. O site é um enorme banco de dados aberto que pode ser modificado por qualquer pessoa e contém metadados completos de muitos seriados em diferentes idiomas. Todos os conteúdos e imagens no site foram contribuições de usuários para usuários e têm um alto padrão de qualidade. O esquema do banco de dados e do site são de código aberto sob a licença GPL.</description>
      <description lang="ro">TheTVDB.com este un colectore TV. Site-ul este o bază de date masivă, deschisă, ce poate fi modificată de oricine şi conţine date complete despre multe seriale în diferite limbi. Tot conţinutul site-ului a fost contribuit de către utilizatori pentru utilizatori şi are un standard de caliate înalt. Schema bazei de date şi site-ul au sursele libere sub licenţă GPL.</description>
      <description lang="ru">TheTVDB.com — это инфоресурс для сериалов. Сайт представляет собой огромную открытую базу данных, в которую может вносить данные любой пользователь и которая содержит полные мета-данные для многих сериалов на различных языках. Всё содержимое и изображения на сайте были выложены его пользователями для других пользователей и имеют высокий уровень качества. Структура базы данных и веб-сайт созданы с открытым исходным кодом по лицензии GPL.</description>
      <description lang="se">TVDB.com är en TV-skrapa. Sajten är en massiv öppen databas som kan ändras av vem som helst och innehåller full metadata för mängder av serier på olika språk. Allt innehåll och bilder på sajten har bidragits av användare för användare och har en hög standard eller kvalitet. Databasschemat och webbsidan är licensierat som GPL.</description>
      <description lang="sk">TheTVDB.com je zdroj získavania dát ohľadom TV. Táto stránka je obrovskou otvorenou databázou, ktorú môže upravovať ktokoľvek a obsahuje úplne metadáta pre mnoho relácií v rôznych jazykoch. Všetok obsah a obrázky na stránke bol dodaný samotnými používateľmi pre používateľov a udržuje si vysoký štandard a kvalitu. Schéma databázy a webová stránka sú dostupné vo forme open source v súlade s licenciou GPL.</description>
      <description lang="sl">TheTVDB.com je ponudnik informacij o TV serijah. Stran je masovna odprta baza podatkov, ki jo lahko dopolni kdorkoli, in vsebuje informacije o najrazličnejših TV serijah v več jezikih. Vsa vsebina in slike so bile dodane s strani uporabnikov in imajo visok nivo kvalitete. Shema baze in spletna stran sta odprtokodni pod GPL.</description>
      <description lang="sq">TheTVDB.com është një "TV Scraper". Kjo faqe është nje bazë e të dhënave e hapur që mund të modifikohet nga si cili dhe përmbanë metadata  për shumë seriale në gjuhë të ndryshme. Gjitha të dhënat dhe imazhet në këtë faqe janë kontribuar nga përdoruesit për përdoruesit dhe kanë një standard dhe kualitet të lartë. Skema e bazës së të dhënave dhe sajti i uebit janë open source nën liçensën GPL.  </description>
      <description lang="sv">TVDB.com är en TV-skrapa. Sajten är en massiv öppen databas som kan bli modifierad av vem som helst och innehåller all metadata för många serier på olika språk. Allt innehåll och bilder på sidan har bidragits av användare för användare och har hög standard eller kvalitet. Databasschemat och sidan är öppen källkod licensierat under GPL.</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">TheTVDB.com ஒரு தொலைக்காட்சி சுரண்டி. இந்த இணையத்தளத்தில் ஒரு பெரிய தரவுத்தளம் உள்ளது. இதில் எல்லா மொழிகளின் மேட்டாடேட்டா உள்ளது. அனைத்து தகவல்களும் படங்களும் அதன் பயனர்களின் சேகரிப்புஆகும். GPL லைசன்சில் உள்ளது.</description>
      <description lang="th">TheTVDB.com เป็นตัวดึงข้อมูลทีวี เว็บไซต์เป็นฐานข้อมูลเปิดขนาดใหญ่ที่สามารถแก้ไขได้โดยทุกคนและมีข้อมูลขั้นสูงเต็มรูปแบบ สำหรับหลาย ๆ รายการ ในแต่ละภาษาที่แตกต่างกัน เนื้อหาและรูปภาพทั้งหมดในเว็บไซต์ ได้รับการสนับสนุนโดยผู้ใช้เพื่อผู้ใช้ มีคุณภาพและมาตรฐานที่สูง schemaของฐานข้อมูลและเว็บไซต์ได้เปิดภายใต้ GPL</description>
      <description lang="tr">TheTVDB.com bir TV Scraper'dır. Bu site herkesin düzenleyebileceği büyük bir açık veritabanıdır ve farklı dillerdeki bir çok şov için bilgiler içerir. Sitedeki her resim ve içerik kullanıcılar tarafından kullanıcılar için karşılanır ve bunlar yüksek standart ve kaliteye sahiptir. Veritabanı şeması ve internet sitesi GPL lisansı altında açık kaynaklıdır.</description>
      <description lang="uk">TheTVDB.com — джерело інформації про серіали. Це величезна база даних, що містить повні метадані про різні серіали багатьма мовами, яку може редагувати будь-хто. Увесь вміст і зображення на сайті, що відповідають найвищим стандартам якості, надали користувачі для користувачів. Схема бази даних і веб-сайт мають відкриті коди на умовах ліцензії GPL.</description>
      <description lang="vi">TheTVDB.com là trình lấy dữ liệu TV show. Site chứa một số lượng khổng lồ cơ sở dữ liệu mở, có thể được thay đổi bởi mọi người và đầy đủ dữ liệu lớn các show trên nhiều ngôn ngữ. Tất cả nội dung và hình ảnh trên site này đều được đóng góp bởi toàn bộ người dùng của nó và có chất lượng cao. Mô hình cơ sở dữ liệu và website đều là mã nguồn mở được hỗ trợ bởi GPL.</description>
      <description lang="zh">TheTVDB.com 是一个电视刮削器。该网站是一个巨大的开放式数据库，任何人都可以修改，包含多语言的许多电视剧集资料。网站设定了高品质标准，所有图片和内容都由用户提供。数据库结构和网站均在 GPL 许可下开源。</description>
      <description lang="zh_TW">TheTVDB.com是一個電視節目。該網站是一個龐大並可以由任何人修改的開放性資料庫，並包含可以以多國語言顯示的完整的數據資料。所有內容和圖片都是經由用戶提供使用，有一定的標準或質量。數據庫架構和網站是在GPL下的開放性源碼。</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL v2.0</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database"
       version="3.8.5"
       provider-name="XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.7.8"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.themoviedb.org" version="2.13.1"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.10" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.movies"
               language="en"
               library="tmdb.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">TMDB Fliek Skraper</summary>
      <summary lang="be">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Сваля инф. за филми от TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador de pel·lícules TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Zdroj zisku dat k filmům TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Ffilmiau TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="da">TMDB Scraper til Film</summary>
      <summary lang="de">TMDB Filmscraper</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Scraper Ταινιών του TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="en">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="en_NZ">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="en_US">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper de Películas TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="et">TMDB Filmi kaabits</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">TMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Collecteur de Films TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur de films TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Scraper de Filme de TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="he">TMDB סקרייפר סרטים</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">TMDB filmski sakupljač informacija</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">TMDB filmadat leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Pengais Film TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="is">TMDB Skafa fyrir Kvikmyndir</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Ricercatore per TMDB Movie</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">TMDB映画のスクレーパー</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">TMDB 영화 정보수집기</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">TMDB filmų skreperis</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">TMDB инфо за филмови</summary>
      <summary lang="ml">മൂവി ഡി ബി, വിവരശേഖരം</summary>
      <summary lang="ms">Pengikis Cakera TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="my">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">TMDb-filmscraper</summary>
      <summary lang="no">TMDB-skraper</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Ekstraktor filmowy TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Colector de filmes TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de Filmes TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Scraper de filme TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Инфоресурс на базе TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">TheMovieDB filmový sťahovač</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Ponudnik informacij o filmih TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">TMDB Filmskrapa</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">LastFM நிகழ்படம் சுரண்டி</summary>
      <summary lang="th">ตัวรับข้อมูลภาพยนต์ TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">TMDB Film Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">TMDB — джерело інформації про фільми</summary>
      <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu Phim từ TMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">TMDB 电影刮削器</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">TMDB 電影搜括器</summary>
      <description lang="af">themoviedb.org is 'n verniet en oop fliek databasis. Dit is totaal gebruiker gedryf deur mense soos jy. TMDB word huidiglik deur miljoene mense elke maand gebruik, en met hulle kragtige API word dit ook deur baie gewilde media sentrums soos Kodi gebruik om Fliek Metadata, Plakkate en Ondersteunerkuns te onttrek om die gebruiker se ondervinding te verryk.</description>
      <description lang="be">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="bg">themoviedb.org е безплатна и отворена филмова база данни. Задвижва се изцяло от потребителите си, от хора като вас. Милиони хора по света всеки месец ползват TMDb. Благодарение на многофункционално API може да се ползва от най-различни и популярни медийни центрове като Kodi, които извличат метаданни, постери и фанарт за филми с цел за красивото оформяне на интерфейса.</description>
      <description lang="ca">themoviedb.org és una base de dades oberta i lliure. Es manté completament per usuaris, per gent com tu. TMDb s'utilitza actualment per milions de persones cada mes i amb la seva potent API també és utilitzada per molts centre media populas com l'Kodi per obtenir les meta-dades de pel·lícules, pósters i fanart per enriquir l'experiència d'usuari.</description>
      <description lang="cs">themoviedb.org je otevřená a svobodná databáze filmů. Je řízena uživateli, tedy lidmi jako vy. TMDB je každý měsíc používána milióny lidí a se svým výborným API je také používano mnoha populárními mediálními centry jako je Kodi, k získávání metadat, plagátů a fanartu filmů pro obohacení uživatelského zážitku.</description>
      <description lang="cy">Mae themoviedb.org yn gronfa ddata ffilmiau rhydd ac agored. Mae'n cael ei yrru gan ddefnyddwyr fel chi. Mae TMDb yn cael ei ddefnyddio gan filiynau o bobl bob mis a gyda'i API pwerus, mae'n cael ei ddefnyddio gan lawer o'r canolfannau cyfrwng fel Kodi i estyn metadata ffilmiau, posteri a chelf er mwyn cyfoethogi profiad defnyddwyr.</description>
      <description lang="da">themoviedb.org er en fri og åben filmdatabase. Den er helt og aldeles brugerdrevet af folk som dig. TMDb bruges i dag af millioner af mennesker hver måned, og med deres kraftfulde API er den også brugt af mange populære mediecentre såsom Kodi til at hente metadata, plakater og fankunst til film, for at berige brugerens oplevelse.</description>
      <description lang="de">TheMovieDB.org ist eine freie und offene Filmdatenbank. Sie wird von Benutzern wie dir angetrieben. TheMovieDB wird zur Zeit von millionen Nutzern jeden Monat genutzt und dank ihrer mächtigen API ist sie auch von vielen Media-Center, wie z.B. Kodi, implementiert, um Film-Metadaten, -Poster und -Fanarts zu beziehen, die das Benutzererlebnis verbessern.</description>
      <description lang="el">Το themoviedb.org είναι μία δωρεάν και ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων ταινιών. Διαχειρίζεται πλήρως από ανθρώπους σαν και εσάς. Το TMDb χρησιμοποιείται από εκατομμύρια ανθρώπους κάθε μήνα, και με το πανίσχυρο API τους, χρησιμοποιείται και από πολλά δημοφιλή κέντρα πολυμέσων όπως το Kodi για να λαμβάνουν μετα-δεδομένα Ταινιών, Αφίσες και Fanart για εμπλουτισμό της εμπειρίας του χρήστη.</description>
      <description lang="en">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="en_NZ">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="en_US">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="es">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Es una página web que se basa en contenido subido por los usuarios. TMDb es usada diariamente por mucha gente gracias a su API, que es usada por más programas aparte de Kodi para descargar información de películas así como Posters o Fanart (Fondos de escritorio basados en películas usados en distintos skins) para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Está  formada con contenido subido por usuarios como vos. TMDb es actualmente utilizada por millones de personas cada mes y, gracias a su poderosa API, es usada por muchos programas populares como Kodi para descargar Información de Películas, Posters y Fanart para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">themoviedb.org es una base de datos de películas gratis y abierta. Es completamente manejada por usuarios y personas como tu. Actualmente TMDb es usada por millones de personas cada mes, y dado a su poderosa API, es usada también por varios media centers populares como Kodi para obtener Metada de Películas, Posters y Fanarts, enriqueciendo de esta manera la experiencia del usuario.</description>
      <description lang="et">themoviedb.org on tasuta ja vaba juurdepääsuga filmide andmebaas.See on täielikult koostatud sinu sarnaste inimeste poolt. TMDb on hetkel igapäevaselt kasutuses miljonite inimeste poolt ja seda kasutavad paljud populaarsed meediakeskused, nagu ka Kodi, filmiandmete, fännikunsti ja posterite leidmiseks.</description>
      <description lang="fi">themoviedb.org on vapaa ja avoin elokuvatietokanta. Se on täysin käyttäjien ylläpitämä. TMDb:a käyttää miljoonat ihmiset joka kuukausi, sitä käytetään käyttäjäkokemuksen rikastuttamiseen monissa muissakin suosituissa Kodi:n kaltaisissa ohjelmissa lataamalla elokuvien tietoja, julisteita ja fanitaidetta.</description>
      <description lang="fr">themoviedb.org est une base de données gratuite et libre d'accès de films. Elle est totalement gérée par les utilisateurs. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et, grâce à ses puissantes fonctions et routines, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux Media Centers populaires comme Kodi aux fins de récupération des Métadonnées, Posters et Fanarts des films en vue d'améliorer l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">themoviedb.org est une base de données libre et ouverte. Elle est complètement gérée par des gens comme vous. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et avec son API puissante, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux centres multimédias populaires comme Kodi pour récupérer les métadonnées des films, les affiches et le fanart afin d'enrichir l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
      <description lang="gl">themoviedb.org é una base de datos sobre filmes libre e aberta, impulsada por xente coma ti. Na actualidade TMDb é usada por millóns de persoas todos os meses, e grazas ó seu potente API, usado por algúns dos centros multimedia máis populares como Kodi para obter a información dos filmes, Posters e Fanart e así mellorar a experiencia do usuario.</description>
      <description lang="he">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="hr">themoviedb.org je besplatna i otvorena baza filmskih podataka. TMDb trenutno koriste milijuni ljudi svaki mjesec uz pomoću njegovog snažnog API-ja, isto tako se koristi u mnogim popularnim medijskim centrima poput Kodi-a, kako bi mogli sakupljati informacije o filmovima, filmske postere, omote filmova i na kraju obogatili korisničko iskustvo.</description>
      <description lang="hu">A themoviedb.org egy ingyenes és nyílt filmadatbázis. Teljes egészében olyan felhasználók töltik fel, mint például Te. A TMDb-t havonta emberek milliói használják és a hatékony API-n keresztül számos népszerű média center is, mint például az Kodi a filmadatok, poszterek, fanartképek letöltésére.</description>
      <description lang="id">themoviedb.org adalah database film yang gratis dan terbuka. Ini benar-benar digerakkan oleh orang-orang seperti Anda. TMDb saat ini digunakan oleh jutaan orang setiap bulannya dan dengan APInya yang digdaya, juga digunakan oleh beberapa pusat media seperti Kodi untuk mengambil Metadata Film, Poster dan Fanart untuk menperkaya pengalaman penggunanya.</description>
      <description lang="is">themoviedb.org er frír og opinn gagnagrunnur. Hann er algjörlega rekinn af fólki eins og þér. TMBd er notaður af milljónum manna í hverjum mánuði og með öflugum forritaskilum þeirra (API), er hann líka notaður af mörgum vinsælum heimabíókerfum eins og Kodi til að ná í Ítarupplýsingar yfir Kvikmyndir, Veggspjöld og Fanart til að lífga upplifun notandans.</description>
      <description lang="it">themoviedb.org è un database libero e aperto. E' gestito da utenti e persone come te. Viene usato correntemente da millioni di persone ogni mese e con le sue potenti API, è anche utilizzato da molti popolari media centers come Kodi per ottenere Metadati, Posters e Fanart di film per arricchire la loro esperienza utente.</description>
      <description lang="ja">themoviedb.org は自由でオープンな映画データベースです。その運営は、完全にユーザ主導で行われています。TMDb は現在毎月何百万人もの人に利用されているほか、Kodi のようなメディアセンターも、TMDb のパワフルな API を介して映画メタデータ、ポスター、ファンアートを取得し、使い勝手を向上させるなどして使っています。</description>
      <description lang="ko">themoviedb.org 는 전적으로 여러분 같은 이용자가 주도하는 무료 공개 영화 데이터베이스입니다. TMDb 는 현재 매월 수백만의 사람들이 강력한 API와 함께 사용하고 있을 뿐만 아니라 Kodi 같은 많은 미디어 센터가 영화 정보, 포스터, 팬아트를 가져와 풍성한 사용자 경험을 제공하는데 이용되고 있습니다.</description>
      <description lang="lt">themoviedb.org yra nemokama ir atvira filmų duomenų bazė. Ji palaikoma tokių pat vartotojų kaip ir jūs. TMDb šiuo metu naudojama milijonų žmonių kiekvieną mėnesį ir turi galingą API, o taip pat naudojama daugelio populiarių media centrų, tokių kaip Kodi, kad gautų filmų metaduomenis, plakatus ir Fanart, siekiant praturtinti vartotojo patirtį.</description>
      <description lang="mk">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
      <description lang="ml">മൂവി ഡി ബി, എല്ലാവർക്കും കൈവക്കാവുന്ന ഒരു സൗജന്യ വിവരശേഖരമാണ്. ഇതുമൂലം ലോകം മുഴുവനും സിനിമാ പോസ്റ്ററുകൾ എല്ലവരും കാണുന്നു</description>
      <description lang="ms">themoviedb.org adalah pangkalan data cakera terbuka. Ia sepenuhnya dipacu oleh individu seperti anda. TMDb buat masa ini diguna oleh berjuta-juta individu setiap bulan dan dengan API hebat mereka, ia juga digunakan oleh banyak pusat media popular seperti Kodi untuk mendapatkan Data Meta, Poster, Seni Peminat Cereka untuk memperkayakan pengalaman pengguna.</description>
      <description lang="nl">Themoviedb.org is een vrije en open filmdatabank. Gebruikers zoals jij vormen de motor van deze site. Op dit moment gebruiken elke maand miljoenen mensen TMDb. De krachtige API van de site laat mediacenters zoals Kodi toe om metadata, posters en fanart op te halen en zo de gebruikerservaring te verrijken.</description>
      <description lang="no">themoviedb.org er en fir og åpen filmdatabase. Den drives helt og fullt av mennesker som deg. TMDB brukes av millioner av mennesker hver måned og med sitt gode API, brukes den også av mange popluære mediasenterløsninger som Kodi for å hente metadata for filmer, plakater og fanart for å gi en bedre brukeropplevelse.</description>
      <description lang="pl">themoviedb.org jest wolną i otwartą filmową bazą danych, zarządzaną przez osoby takie jak Ty. Obecnie odwiedzają ją miliony osób miesięcznie, a dzięki dostępności interfejsu programistycznego jest używana przez wiele centrów multimedialnych takich jak Kodi, jako źródło informacji o filmach, plakatów i tapet.</description>
      <description lang="pt">O themoviedb.org é uma base de dados de filmes livre e aberta. É actualizado inteiramente por pessoas como você e usado por milhões todos os meses. Com o poderoso motor de busca disponível, também se tornou no favorito para muitos programas de centro de média, como o popular Kodi, para obter informação, posters e fanart que enriquecem a experiência do utilizador.</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">O themoviedb.org é um banco de dados aberto e gratuito. É completamente operado por pessoas como você. O TMDb é atualmente usado por milhares de pessoas a cada mês e com sua poderosa API, é usado por muitas centrais de mídia populares como o Kodi para buscar metadados, cartazes e fanart de filmes para enriquecer a experiência do usuário.</description>
      <description lang="ro">themoviedb.org este o bază de date de filme gratuită și deschisă. Este actualizată de oameni ca și tine. TMDb este curent folosită de milioane de oameni în fiecare lună și datorită API-ului puternic, este de asemena folosită de multe centre media populare ca Kodi pentru a obține informații despre filme, afișe și imagini produse de fani (Fanart) care îmbogățesc experiența utilizatorului.</description>
      <description lang="ru">themoviedb.org — это бесплатная и открытая база данных фильмов. Она полностью поддерживается обычными людьми. В данный момент сайт TMDb используют миллионы людей каждый месяц, и благодаря мощному API его могут использовать различные популярные медиацентры, такие как Kodi, чтобы получать метаданные, постеры и фанарт для фильмов с целью красивого оформления интерфейса.</description>
      <description lang="se">themoviedb.org är en fri och öppen filmdatabas. Det drivs helt av människor som dig. TMDb används av miljontals människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API, är det också använt av många populära mediacenter som Kodi för att hämta filmmetadata, omslag och fanart för att förgylla användarens upplevelse.</description>
      <description lang="sk">themoviedb.org je voľná a otvorená databáza filmov. Je výlučne vedená užívateľmi ako si ty. TMDb je každý mesiac používaná miliónmi ľudí, a vďaka svojmu výkonnému API je veľmi populárna medzi 'media centrami' ako Kodi pre sťahovanie filmových metadát, plagátov a fanartov pre obohatenie  zážitkov.</description>
      <description lang="sl">themoviedb.org je brezplačna in prosta baza filmov. Je v celoti ustvarjena s strani uporabnikov kot ste vi. TMDB uporablja miljone ljudi in z njihovo močno API, jo lahko uporabljate tudi v multimedijskih centrih kot Kodi, s tem prenesete informacije o filmih, plakate in ozadja ter s tem popestrite uporabniško izkušnjo.</description>
      <description lang="sv">themoviedb.org är en gratis och öppen filmdatabas. Den drivs helt av människor som du. TMDb används för närvarande av miljoner människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API används den även av många populära mediacenter som t.ex. Kodi för att hämta metadata om filmer, affischer och fanart för att berika användarens upplevelse.</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">themoviedb.org ஒரு இலவச மற்றும் திறந்த திரைப்பட தரவுத்தளம் ஆகும். இந்த தரவுத்தளம்  முற்றிலும் பயனர் மக்களால் இயக்கப்படுகிறது. TMDb அவர்களது சக்திவாய்ந்த API இனால் தற்போது பல இலட்சக்கணக்கான மக்களால் ஒவ்வொரு மாதமும் பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது, இது Kodi போன்ற பல பிரபல ஊடக மையங்களில் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்த பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது.</description>
      <description lang="th">themoviedb.org เป็นฐานข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ที่ฟรีและเปิดกว้าง. มันถูกขับเคลื่อนจากผู้ใช้ โดยคนเช่นคุณ. TMDb ปัจจุบันมีการใช้โดยคนนับล้านในแต่ละเดือน และมีประสิทธิภาพด้วย API ของพวกเขา , มันยังถูกใช้โดยหลายศูนย์สื่อที่นิยมเช่น Kodi เพื่อดึง อธิบายข้อมูลภาพยนตร์, โปสเตอร์และ แฟนอาร์ต เพื่อเพิ่มประสบการณ์ของผู้ใช้</description>
      <description lang="tr">themoviedb.org ücretsiz ve herkese açık bir film veri tabanıdır. Tamamen kullanıcılar tarafından oluşturulmakta ve yönetilmektedir. TMDb her ay milyonlarca kullanıcı tarafından kullanılmakta ve güçlü API'si sayesinde Kodi gibi bir çok popüler medya merkezi tarafından Film Veritabanı, Poster ve Fanart bilgilerini kullanarak kullanıcı deneyimini zenginleştirmektedir.</description>
      <description lang="uk">themoviedb.org - це безкоштовна і відкрита база даних фільмів. Вона повністю підтримується звичайними людьми. В даний момент сайт TMDb використовують мільйони людей кожен місяць, і завдяки потужному API, його можуть використовувати різні популярні медіацентри, такі як Kodi, щоб отримувати метадані, постери і фанарт для фільмів з метою оформлення інтерфейсу.</description>
      <description lang="vi">themoviedb.org là cơ sở dữ liệu về phim ảnh mở và miễn phí. Nó hoàn toàn được kiểm soát bởi những người như bạn. TMDb hiện tại đang được sử dụng bởi hàng triệu người dùng hàng tháng và với sự hỗ trợ của bộ API mạnh mẽ nó cũng được sử dụng bởi những thiết bị giải trí cá nhân như Kodi cho việc lấy dữ liệu về Phim ảnh, Poster và Fanart để làm tăng trải nghiệm của người sử dụng</description>
      <description lang="zh">themoviedb.org 是一个开放和自由的电影数据库。它完全由象你一样的用户来掌控。TMDb 每月为上百万用户提供服务，并通过强大的 API 界面为许多流行的媒体中心系统如 Kodi 提供电影资料、封面海报和同人画以丰富用户的体验。</description>
      <description lang="zh_TW">themoviedb.org是一個免費和開放的電影資料庫。它是完全由與您一樣的廣大使用者來更新資訊。 TMDb目前擁有數以百萬計的使用人次並且有著強大的API，許多受歡迎的媒體中心平台像Kodi藉由TMDb獲取電影的數據資料庫，海報和影片資訊，以豐富使用者體驗。</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL v2.0</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.musicvideos.theaudiodb.com"
       name="TheAudioDb.com for Music Videos"
       version="1.2.7"
       provider-name="XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
      <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.7.3"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.musicvideos"
               language="en"
               library="tadb.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">theaudiodb.com Musiek Video Skraper</summary>
      <summary lang="be">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Сваля инф. за музикални клипове от theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador de vídeos musicals de theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Zdroj dat o hudebních videích theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Fideo Cerddoriaeth theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="da">theaudiodb.com Musikvideo-scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="de">theaudiodb.com Musikvideo Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Scraper Μουσικών Βίντεο του theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="en">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="en_NZ">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="en_US">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Buscador de videoclips de theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Videos de Música de theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="et">theaudiodb.com muusikavideo kraabits</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">theaudiodb.com musiikkivideotietojen lataaja</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">theaudiodb.com Scraper Clip Vidéo</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur de vidéos musicales pour theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Scraper de vídeo e música de theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="he">theaudiodb.com סקרייפר וידאו קליפ</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">theaudiodb.com sakupljač za glazbene spotove</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">theaudiodb.com videóklip leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Pengais Video Musik theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="is">theaudiodb.com Skafa fyrir Tónlistarmyndbönd</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Lo scraper di video musicali theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">theaudiodb.com 音楽ビデオスクレーパー</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">theaudiodb.com 뮤직 비디오 정보수집기</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">theaudiodb.com muzikinių vaizdo klipų skreperis</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="ms">Pengikis Video Muzik theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="my">theaudiodb.com Music Video Scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">theaudiodb.com Muziekvideo-scraper</summary>
      <summary lang="no">theaudiodb.com Skraper for musikkvideo</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper teledysków theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Colector de música theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de concertos theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Informaţii videoclipuri de la theaudiodb.com </summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Скрапер музыки и видео theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för theaudiodb.com musik</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Zdroj získavania dát o hudobných videách zo stránky theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Ponudnik informacij o videospotih theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">theaudiodb.com musikvideoskrapa</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">theaudiodb.com இசை நிகழ்படம் சுரண்டி</summary>
      <summary lang="th">ตัวดึงข้อมูลวิดีโอเพลง theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">Здирач музичного відео з theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu video nhạc từ theaudiodb.com</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">theaudiodb.com 音乐电视刮削器</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">theaudiodb.com音樂影片搜括器</summary>
      <description lang="af">Laai Musiek Video informasie af</description>
      <description lang="am">የሙዚቃ ቪዲዮ መረጃ ማውረጃ</description>
      <description lang="be">Download Music Video information</description>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за музикални клипове</description>
      <description lang="ca">Baixa informació de videos musicals</description>
      <description lang="cs">Zdroj dat stahující informace o hudebních videích z TheAudioDB.com. Kvůli složitým problémům s vyhledáváním požaduje nástroj pro vyhledávání název složky složky/souboru pojmenován jako 'umělec - název stopy', pokud tomu tak není, nenalezne žádné výsledky.</description>
      <description lang="cy">Mae'r crafwr yn llwytho i lawr gwybodaeth am Gerddoriaeth Fideo o TheAudioDB.com. Oherwydd amryw o anawsterau chwilio mae'r crafwr yn disgwyl i'r ffolder/enw ffeil fod wedi ei fformatio fel 'artist - enw track' neu ni fydd yn dychwelyd canlyniadau.</description>
      <description lang="da">Hent Musikvideo-information</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieser Scraper lädt Musikvideoinformationen von TheAudioDB.com herunter. Aufgrund diverser Suchschwierigkeiten erwartet der Scraper derzeit, dass Ordner/Dateinamen als 'Künstler - Songname' formatiert werden, andernfalls wird er keine Ergebnisse zurückliefern.</description>
      <description lang="el">Λήψη πληροφοριών Μουσικών Βίντεο</description>
      <description lang="en">This scraper is downloading Music Video information from TheAudioDB.com. Due to various search difficulties the scraper currently expects the folder/filename to be formatted as 'artist - trackname' otherwise it will not return results.</description>
      <description lang="en_NZ">This scraper is downloading Music Video information from TheAudioDB.com. Due to various search difficulties the scraper currently expects the folder/filename to be formatted as 'artist - trackname' otherwise it will not return results.</description>
      <description lang="en_US">This scraper is downloading Music Video information from TheAudioDB.com. Due to various search difficulties the scraper currently expects the folder/filename to be formatted as 'artist - trackname' otherwise it will not return results.</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga información del videoclip</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">Descarga información del Video Clip</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">Descarga Información de Vídeos de Músca</description>
      <description lang="et">Hankija laeb alla muusikavideo infot portaalist TheAudioDB.com. Mitmete otsinguohtude tõttu tuvastab hankija kausta/faili nime vormingus 'esitaja - loo nimi', muidu hankija ei suuda otsimist läbi viia.</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkivideoiden tiedot</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharger les informations des clips vidéos</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur télécharge les informations sur les vidéos musicales depuis TheAudioDB.com. À cause de difficultés de recherche diverses, l'extracteur s'attend présentement à ce que le dossier/nom du fichier soit formaté comme « artiste - nom de la piste ». Aucun résultat ne sera retourné si ce n'est pas le cas.</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este scraper descarga a información dende TheAudioDB.com. Debido a algúns problemas o scraper agarda que o cartafol/nome do ficheiro teña o formato 'artista - nome da pista' ou non retornará resultados.</description>
      <description lang="he">הורד מידע וידאו קליפ</description>
      <description lang="hr">Ovaj sakupljač preuzima informacije o glazbenim spotovima s TheAudioDB.com. Uslijed mnogih problema s pretragom sakupljač očekuje da mape i datoteke budu u formatu 'izvođač - naziv pjesme' ili neće dati rezultata.</description>
      <description lang="hu">Videóklip információk letöltése a theaudiodb.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="id">Pengais sedang mengunduh informasi musik video dari TheAudioDB.com. Dikarenakan berbagai kesulitan pencarian, Pengais mengharapkan folder/nama-berkas dalam format 'artis-judullagu' Apabila tidak, hasil tidak dapat muncul.</description>
      <description lang="is">Þessi skafa halar niður upplýsingum Tónlistarmyndbanda frá TheAudioDB.com. Vegna ýmissa vandamála með leit þá gerir þessi skafa ráð fyrir að möppu/skráarnafn sé á forminu 'Listamaður - laganafn' annars skilar hún engum niðurstöðum.</description>
      <description lang="it">Scarica informazioni Video Musicale</description>
      <description lang="ja">このスクレイパーはTheAudioDB.comから音楽ビデオ情報をダウンロードしています。様々な検索の困難のため、スクレイパーは現在「アーティスト - 曲名」とフォーマットされているフォルダ/ファイルネームを期待しています。そうでなければ、結果を返しません。</description>
      <description lang="ko">이 정보수집기믄 TheAudioDB.com에서 뮤직 비디오 정보를 가져옵니다. 여러가지 검색상의 어려움 때문에 폴더/파일이름이 '아티스트-트랙이름'으로 지정되어야 합니다. 그렇지 않으면 결과를 가져올 수 없습니다.</description>
      <description lang="lt">Šis skreperis atsiunčia muzikinių vaizdo klipų informaciją iš TheAudioDB.com. Dėl įvairių paieškos sunkumų, aplanko/failo pavadinimo formatas turi būti 'atlikėjas - takelio pavadinimas'. Priešingu atvejus nebus rasta jokių rezultatų.</description>
      <description lang="mk">Превземи информации за музичко видео</description>
      <description lang="ms">Pengikis ini memuat turun maklumat Video Muzik dari TheAudioDB.com. Oleh kerana kesukaran menggelintar, pengikis biasanya jangkakan folder/namafail diformat sebagai 'artis - namatrek' jika tidak ia tidak akan kembalikan keputusan.</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze scraper download muziekvideo-informatie van TheAudioDB.com. Vanwege diverse zoek moeilijkheden verwacht de scraper nu dat de map/bestandsnaam is genaamd als 'artiest - Titel' anders zal het geen resultaten tonen.</description>
      <description lang="no">Last ned musikkvideoinformasjon</description>
      <description lang="pl">Scraper teledysków pobiera informacje z bazy TheAudioDB.com. Ze względu na różne trudności wyszukiwania, scraper obecnie wymaga aby folder/plik był sformatowany: "artysta - nazwa ścieżki" inaczej nie zadziała poprawnie.</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Download de informação de Concertos</description>
      <description lang="ro">Acest plugin descarcă informaţii despre videoclipuri de la TheAudioDB.com. Datorita dificultatilor de cautare, pluginul asteapta ca perechea director/nume fisier sa fie formatate ca 'artist - nume piesa' altfel nu va returna nici un rezultat.</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать сведения о видеоклипах</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikvideoinformation från theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj dát získava informácie o hudobných videách zo stránky TheAudioDB.com. Z dôvodu rôznych problémov pri hľadaní, zdroj dát aktuálne očakáva, aby bol názov priečinka/súboru formátovaný ako 'interpret - názov_skladby', v opačnom prípade nevráti žiadne výsledky.</description>
      <description lang="sl">Prenesite informacije o videospotih z TheAudioDB.com. Zaradi težavnosti iskanja morajo biti mape/datoteke v formatu 'izvajalec - pesem', drugače informacije ne bodo najdene.</description>
      <description lang="sv">Ladda ner musikvideoinformation</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த வலை சுரண்டி TheAudioDB.com இல் இருந்து இசை வீடியோ தகவல்களை பதிவிறக்கம் செய்கிறது. பல்வேறு தேடல் சிரமங்கள் காரணமாக தற்போது இந்த வலை சுரண்டியானது கோப்புறை / கோப்பு பெயரை 'கலைஞர் - தடங்கள் பெயர்' எனவாக வடிவமைக்க வேண்டும் என்று எதிர்பார்க்கிறது இல்லையெனில் முடிவுகளை தராது. கலைஞர் அல்லது தடங்கள் பெயரில் '-' அடையாளம் இருந்தால் அதை கூட கண்டுபிடிக்க முடியாது.</description>
      <description lang="th">ดาวน์โหลดข้อมูลวิดีโอเพลง</description>
      <description lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu đang tải thông tin video nhạc từ nguồn TheAudioDB.com. Do nhiều khó khăn tìm kiếm khác nhau, trình lấy dữ liệu này hiện chỉ hỗ trợ định dạng thư mục/tên tệp tin theo mẫu 'nghệ sỹ - tên track' nếu không sẽ không trả lại kết quả.</description>
      <description lang="zh">从 theaudiodb.com 下载音乐电视资料。为简化搜索，刮削器限定文件夹/文件名格式为“歌手 - 歌名”，否则将不会返回结果。</description>
      <description lang="zh_TW">此搜括器是從 TheAudioDB.com下載取得音樂影片資訊。因為各種不同搜尋變數，此搜括器目前須將資料夾／檔案名稱 重新命名為 "演出者－歌曲資訊"否則將無法正常取得專輯資料。帶有'-"符號的演出者或歌曲資訊也有極高可能無法找到。</description>
      <license>GPL v2.0</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=136105</forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database Scraper Library"
       version="2.13.1"
       provider-name="XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="tmdb.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="en">TMDb Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de peliculas de TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">TMDb elokuvatietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">TMDb leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">TMDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för TMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">TMDb刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля миниатюри и fanarts от www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="en">Download thumbs and fanarts from www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga posters y fanart de www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa pienoiskuvia ja fanitaidetta www.themoviedb.org -sivustolta</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharge vignettes et backdrops depuis www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="hu">Bélyeg- és fanartképek letöltése a www.themoviedb.org webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Miniaturen en fanart ophalen van www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj ikony i fanarty z www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="ro">Descărcați miniaturi și imagini realizate de fani de pe www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать миниатюры и фанарт с www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner miniatyrer och fanart från www.themoviedb.org</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.themoviedb.org下载海报和同人画</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com"
         name="TheAudioDb Common Scraper Functions"
         version="1.7.3"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="tadb.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="en">TheAudioDb Music Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für TheAudioDb.org</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">TheAudioDb musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper TheAudioDb pour la musique</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">TheAudioDb zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">TheAudioDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация TheAudioDb</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TheAudioDb.org</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">TheAudioDb音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.theaudiodb.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.theaudiodb.com</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.theaudiodb.com下载音乐信息</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org"
       name="MusicBrainz Scraper Library"
        version="2.0.4"
       provider-name="XBMC Foundation">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="musicbrainz.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="en">MusicBrainz Music Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für musicbrainz.org</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">MusicBrainz musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper MusicBrainz pour la musique</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">MusicBrainz zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">MusicBrainz-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация MusicBrainz</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för musicbrainz.org</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">MusicBrainz音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.musicbrainz.org webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.musicbrainz.org</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.musicbrainz.org下载音乐信息</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.last.fm"
         name="Last.FM"
         version="1.6.1"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="lastfm.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="en">LastFM Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">LastFM musiikkitietojen lataaja</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">LastFM leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">LastFM-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för LastFM</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">LastFM刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Musik informationen von www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="es">Descargar información musical de www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharge les infos musicales depuis www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.last.fm webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Muziekinfo ophalen van LastFM</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.last.fm</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.last.fm下载音乐信息</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.imdb.com"
         name="IMDB Scraper Library"
         version="2.7.8"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="imdb.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от IMDB</summary>
      <summary lang="en">IMDB Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">IMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">IMDB leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="kr">IMDB 스크래퍼 라이브러리</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">IMDB Scraper Bibliotheek</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper IMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes IMDb</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för IMDB</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за филми от www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="en">Download Movie information from www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa elokuvatietoja osoitteesta www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="hu">Film információk letöltése a www.imdb.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="kr">www.imdb.com 에서 영화 정보 다운로드</description>
      <description lang="nl">Download film informatie van www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o filmach z www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.imdb.com</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner filminformation från www.imdb.com</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com"
         name="HTBackdrops"
         version="1.3.2"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="htbackdrops.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="en">HTBackdrops Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Scraper für Hintergründe von HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">HTBackdrops taustakuvalataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">HTBackdrops leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">HTBackdrops-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Biblioteca de fundos HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Обработчик Фоновых изображений с HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för HTBackdrops</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">HTBackdrops刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля декорации от www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="en">Download backdrops from www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Hintergründe von www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga fanart y fotos de artistas de www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa taustakuvia osoitteesta www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharge les backdrops depuis www.htbackgrops.com</description>
      <description lang="hu">Fanartképek letöltése www.htbackdrops.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Achtergronden ophalen van www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj tła z www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar fundos de www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать фоновые изображения с www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner bakgrundsbilder från www.htbackdrops.com</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.htbackdrops.com下载背景图</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.hdtrailers.net"
         name="HD-Trailers common scraper functions"
         version="2.0.5"
         provider-name="Olympia">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="hdtrailers.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">HD-Trailers.net Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Scraper für Trailer von HD-Trailers.net</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de Trailers de HD-Trailers.net</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper HD-Trailers.net pour les bande-annonces</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">HD-Trailers.net leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">HD-Trailers.net Scraper Collectie</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper zwiastunów HD-Trailers.net</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de trailers de HD-Trailers.net</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для трейлеров с HD-Trailers.net</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">HD-Trailers.net刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="en">Download Movie Trailers from www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Trailer von www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga trailers de www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharge les bande-annonces de films depuis www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="hu">Filmelőzetesek letöltése a www.hd-trailers.net-ről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Download trailers van www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj zwiastuny filmowe z www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar trailers de www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать трейлеры с www.hd-trailers.net</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.hd-trailers.net下载电影预告片</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.fanart.tv"
         name="fanart.tv Scraper Library"
         version="3.1.1"
         provider-name="Team-Kodi">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="fanarttv.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="en">fanart.tv Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Scraper für Hintergründe von fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">fanart.tv taustakuvalataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">fanart.tv leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">fanart.tv-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Biblioteca de fundos fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Обработчик Фоновых изображений с fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för fanart.tv</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">fanart.tv刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Сваля декорации от www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="en">Download backdrops from www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Hintergründe von www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga fanart y fotos de artistas de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa taustakuvia osoitteesta www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharge les backdrops depuis www.htbackgrops.com</description>
      <description lang="hu">Fanartképek letöltése www.fanart.tv.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Achtergronden ophalen van www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj tła z www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar fundos de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать фоновые изображения с www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner bakgrundsbilder från www.fanart.tv.com</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.fanart.tv.com下载背景图</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.amazon.de"
         name="Amazon.de"
         version="1.0.2"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="amazonde.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="en">amazon.de Scraper Library</summary>
      <description lang="en">Download Music information from amazon.de</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="metadata.common.allmusic.com"
         name="AllMusic"
          version="3.0.2"
         provider-name="Team XBMC">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
               library="allmusic.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>20000</minversion>
      <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="en">AllMusic Music Scraper Library</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für AllMusic.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">AllMusic musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Scraper AllMusic pour la musique</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">AllMusic zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">AllMusic-scraperfuncties</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация AllMusic</summary>
      <summary lang="se">Skrapa för AllMusic.com</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">AllMusic音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
      <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.allmusic.com webhelyről</description>
      <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.allmusic.com</description>
      <description lang="zh">从www.allmusic.com下载音乐信息</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.navi-x"
       name="Navi-X"
       version="3.8.2"
       provider-name="Team Navi-X and XBMCHUB.com">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="repository.xbmchub" optional="true" />
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver"  />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" >
      <provides>executable video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup">
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <minversion>28764</minversion>
      <summary>Media Browser Addon for XBMC.</summary>
      <description>Navi-X is the oldest and most trusted add-on for XBMC, used by millions of people worldwide. You'll find everything from live television to your favourite movies and television shows, easily accessible.</description>
      <disclaimer>http://www.navixtreme.com/terms/</disclaimer>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/forums/38-NAVI-X-MEDIA-BROWSER</forum>
      <website>http://www.navixtreme.com/</website>
      <source></source>
      <email></email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.iheart" name="iHeartRadio" version="0.0.2" provider-name="divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.0"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Live radio over the internet</summary>
      <description>
        Listen to more than 1,500 live radio stations from coast-to-coast including pop, country, urban, rock, talk, and college.[CR]
        Browse radio stations by music genre and location.[CR]
        Read more: http://news.iheart.com/about/
      </description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/divingmule/plugin.audio.iheart</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=170721</forum>
      <disclaimer>These Streams will only work from a U.S. IP address.</disclaimer>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.jazzradio.com"
       name="JazzRadio.com"
       version="3.0.0"
       provider-name="qualisoft.dk - Tim C. Steinmetz">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GPL 2.0</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=144627</forum>
      <website>http://qualisoft.dk</website>
      <source>https://github.com/Bitcrusher/Jazzradio-com-XBMC-plugin.git</source>
      <summary lang="en">JazzRadio.com</summary>
      <description lang="en">
        Presenting jazz radio channels for your enjoyment. Listen for free and enjoy countless hours of the best jazz music around
      </description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.radio_de" name="Radio" version="2.3.0" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://www.radio.de</website>
      <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.audio.radio_de</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=119362</forum>
      <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <summary lang="be">Access &gt;7000 radio broadcasts</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">accedeix a mes de 7000 emissores de radio</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Få adgang til &gt;7000 radioudsendelser</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Zugriff auf &gt;7000 Radiosender</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Πρόσβαση σε πάνω από 7000 εκπομπές</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Access &gt;7000 radio broadcasts</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Escuche más de 7.000 emisoras de radio</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Ecoutez plus de 7000 stations de radio</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Escoite máis de 7000 emisoras de radio</summary>
      <summary lang="he">גישה ליותר מ-7000 שידורי רדיו</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Pristup &gt;7000 radio emitiranja</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Hozzáférés 7000-nél is több rádióadáshoz</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Akses &gt;7000 siaran radio</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Accedi a più di 7000 trasmissioni radio</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Prieiga&gt; 7000 radijo transliacijų</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Toegang tot &gt;7000 radio uitzendingen</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Dostęp do ponad 7000 stacji radiowych</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Aceder a mais de 7000 transmissões de rádio</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Acesse&gt;7000 broadcasts rádios</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Pristupujte k vyše 7000 vysielaniam</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Access &gt;7000 radiosändningar</summary>
      <summary lang="ta_IN">7000 க்கும் மேல் வானொலி ஒளிபரப்புகளை அணுகவும்</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">访问大于7000个电台广播</summary>
      <description lang="be">Music plugin to access over 7000 international radio broadcasts from rad.io, radio.de and radio.fr[CR]Currently features[CR]- English, german and french translated[CR]- Browse stations by location, genre, topic, country, city and language[CR]- Search for stations[CR]- 115 genres, 59 topics, 94 countrys, 1010 citys, 63 languages</description>
      <description lang="ca">Plugin de música per escoltar més de 7000 emissores de ràdio internacionals des rad.io, radio.de i radio.fr. [CR] Característiques: [CR]- Traduccions a l'anglès, alemany, francès i espanyol. [CR]- Cercador de emissores per ubicació, gènere, tema, país, ciutat o idioma. [CR]- Cercador d'emissores. [CR]- 115 gèneres, 59 temes, 94 països, 1010 ciutats, 63 idiomes.</description>
      <description lang="da">Musikplugin som giver adgang til over 7000 internationale radioudsendelser fra rad.io, radio.de og radio.fr[CR]Nuværende funktioner[CR]- Oversat til engelsk, tysk og fransk[CR]- Gennemse stationer efter lokalitet, genre, emne, land, by og sprog[CR]- Søg efter stationer[CR]- 115 genrer, 59 emner, 94 lande, 1010 byer og 63 sprog</description>
      <description lang="de">Das Radio im Internet mit über 7000 Radiosendern, Internetradio Stationen, gratis Streams und Podcasts live von rad.io, radio.de und radio.fr.[CR]Features[CR]- Auf deutsch, englisch und französisch übersetzt[CR]- Sortiert nach: in der Nähe, Genre, Thema, Land und Sprache[CR]- nach Sendern suchen[CR]- 115 Genre, 59 Themen, 94 Länder, 1010 Städte, 63 Sprachen</description>
      <description lang="el">Μουσικό plugin για πρόσβαση σε περισσότερους από 7000 διεθνείς ραδιοφωνικές εκπομπές από τα rad.io, radio.de και radio.fr[CR]Υποστηρίζονται[CR]- Μεταφράσεις σε Αγγλικά, Γερμανικά και Γαλλικά[CR]- Περιήγηση σταθμών ανά τοποθεσία, είδος, θέμα, χώρα, πόλη και γλώσσα[CR]- Αναζήτηση σταθμών[CR]- 115 είδη, 59 θέματα, 94 χώρες, 1010 πόλεις, 63 γλώσσες</description>
      <description lang="en">Music plugin to access over 7000 international radio broadcasts from rad.io, radio.de and radio.fr[CR]Currently features[CR]- English, german and french translated[CR]- Browse stations by location, genre, topic, country, city and language[CR]- Search for stations[CR]- 115 genres, 59 topics, 94 countrys, 1010 citys, 63 languages</description>
      <description lang="es">Plugin de música para escuchar más de 7.000 emisoras de radio internacionales desde rad.io, radio.de y radio.fr.[CR]Características:[CR]- Traducciones al inglés, alemán, francés y español.[CR]- Buscador de emisoras por ubicación, género, tema, país, ciudad o idioma.[CR]- Buscador de emisoras.[CR]- 115 géneros, 59 temas, 94 países, 1.010 ciudades, 63 idiomas.</description>
      <description lang="fr">Plugin musical pour écouter plus de 7000 stations de radio internationales de rad.io, radio.de et radio.fr[CR]Fonctionnalités[CR]- Traduit en Anglais, Allemand et Français[CR]- Parcourir les stations par genre, thème, pays, ville et langue[CR]- Recherche de stations[CR]- 115 genres, 59 thèmes, 94 pays, 1010 villes, 63 langues</description>
      <description lang="gl">Engadido de música para escoitar máis de 7000 emisoras de radio internacionais de rad.io, radio.de e radio.fr.[CR]Características:[CR]- Traducións ao inglés, alemán, francés e castelán.[CR]- Busca de emisoras por localización, xénero, tema, país, cidade ou idioma.[CR]- Busca de emisoras.[CR]- 115 xéneros, 59 temas, 94 países, 1010 cidades, 63 idiomas.</description>
      <description lang="he">הרחבת מוזיקה המאפשרת גישה ליותר מ-7000 שידורי רדיו בינלאומים מ-rad.io, radio.de ו-radio.fr[CR]מאפיינים נוכחיים[CR]- שפות אנגלית, גרמנית וצרפתית[CR]- עיון לפי מיקום, סגנון, נושא, מדינה, עיר ושפה[CR]- חיפוש תחנות[CR]- 115 סגנונות, 59 נושאים, 94 מדינות 1010 ערים, 63 שפות</description>
      <description lang="hr">Glazbeni dodatak za pristup 7000 međunarodnih radio stanica na rad.io, radio.de i radio.fr[CR]Trenutne značajke[CR]- engleski, njemački i francuski prijevodi[CR]- Pregledavajte stanice prema lokaciji, žanru, temi, zemlji, gradu i jeziku[CR]- Pretraživanje stanica[CR]- 115 žanrova, 59 tema, 94 zemalja, 1010 gradova, 63 jezika</description>
      <description lang="hu">Beépülő modul több, mint 7000 nemzetközi rádióadás eléréséhez a rad.io, radio.de és radio.fr oldalakról[CR]Jelenlegi tulajdonságok[CR]- Angol, német, francia és magyar nyelv[CR]- Állomások böngészése hely, műfaj, téma, ország, város és nyelv szerint[CR]- Állomások keresése[CR]- 115 műfaj, 59 téma, 94 ország, 1010 város, 63 nyelv</description>
      <description lang="id">Plugin musik untuk mengakses lebih dari 7000 siaran radio internasional dari rad.io, radio.de dan radio.fr[CR]Fitur saat ini[CR]- Terjemahan Inggris, Jerman dan Perancis[CR]- Jelajah stasiun berdasarkan lokasi, tema, topik, negara, kota dan bahasa[CR]- Cari stasiun[CR]- 115 tema, 59 topik, 94 negara, 1010 kota, 63 bahasa</description>
      <description lang="it">Plugin per accedere a oltre 7000 trasmissioni internazionali radiofoniche da rad.io, radio.de e radio.fr[CR]Caratteristiche[CR]- Supporta inglese, tedesco e francese[CR]- Sfoglia le stazioni per località, genere, argomento, paese, citta e lingua[CR]- Ricerca delle stazioni[CR]- 115 generi, 59 argomenti, 94 paesi, 1010 città e 63 lingue</description>
      <description lang="lt">Muzikos įskiepio prieiga prie daugiau nei 7000 tarptautinių radijo transliacijų iš rad.io, radio.de ir radio.fr [CR] Šiuo metu programoja išversta į [Cr] - anglų, vokiečių ir prancūzų kalbas [CR] - Naršyti stotis pagal: vietovę, žanrą, temą, šalį, miestą ir/ar kalbą [CR] - Ieškoti radio stočių pagal:[Cr] - 115 žanrai, 59 temos, 94 šalys, 1010 miestų, 63 kalbos</description>
      <description lang="nl">muziek plug-in om toegang te krijgen tot over 7000 internationale radiouitzendingen van rad.io, radio.de en radio.fr[CR]Huidige functies[CR]- engels, duits en frans vertaalt[CR]- Zoek naar stations vanuit locatie, genre, onderwerp, land, plaats en taal[CR]- zoek voor stations[CR]- 115 genres. 59 onderwerpen, 94 landen. 1010 plaatsen, 63 talen</description>
      <description lang="pl">Wtyczka muzyczna dająca dostęp do ponad 7000 międzynarodowych stacji radiowych z[CR]rad.io, radio.de, daio.fr[CR]Obecnie w językach[CR]- Angielski, Niemiecki i Francuski[CR]- Szukaj stacji według lokacji, gatunku, tematu, kraju, miasta czy języka[CR]- 115 gatunków, 59 tematów, 94 kraje, 1010 miasta, 63 języki</description>
      <description lang="pt">Plugin de música para aceder a mais de 7000 transmissões de rádio internacionais de rad.io, radio.de e radio.fr[CR]Actualmente, disponibiliza:[CR]- Traduções em vários idiomas[CR]- Navegar estações por localização, género, tópico, país, cidade e idioma[CR]- Procurar por estações[CR]- 115 géneros, 59 tópicos, 94 países, 1010 cidades, 63 idiomas</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Plugin de música para acessar mais de 7000 emissoras de rádio internacionais de rad.io, radio.de e radio.fr [CR] Principais características [CR] - Inglês, Alemão e Francês traduzido [CR] - Procure estações por localização, gênero, tópico, país , cidade e  linguagem [CR] - Procure estações [CR] - 115 gêneros, 59 temas, 94 países, 1010 cidades, 63 idiomas</description>
      <description lang="sk">Hudobný doplnok na prístup k vyše 7000 medzinárodným rádio vysielaniam z rad.io, radio.de a radio.fr&#10;Momentálne podporuje:&#10;- anglické, nemecké a francúzske preklady&#10;- prehliadanie staníc podľa umiestnenia, žánru, témy, krajiny, mesta a jazyka&#10;- vyhľadávanie staníc&#10;- 115 žánrov, 59 tém, 94 krajín, 1010 miest, 63 jazykov</description>
      <description lang="sv">Musiktillägg som ger åtkomst till över 7000 internationella radiosändningar från rad.io, radio.de och radio.fr[CR]Nuvarande funktioner[CR]- Engelsk, tysk, svensk och fransk översättning[]- Bläddra efter stationer baserat på genre, ämne, land, stad och språk[CR]- Sök efter stationer[CR]-115 genres, 59 ämnen, 94 länder, 1010 städer, 63 språk</description>
      <description lang="ta_IN">இசை துணை பயன் rad.io, radio.de மற்றும் radio.fr இருந்து 7000 க்கும் மேல் வானொலி ஒளிபரப்புகளை அணுக உதவி செய்யும்[CR]தற்போதைய அம்சங்கள்[CR]- ஆங்கிலம், ஜெர்மன் மற்றும் பிரெஞ்சு மொழியாக்கம்[CR]- இருப்பிடம், வகை, தலைப்பு, நாடு, நகரம் மற்றும் மொழி கொண்டு நிலையங்களை உலாவ முடியும்[CR]- நிலையங்களை தேடுதல்[CR]- 115 வகைகள், 59 தலைப்புகள், 94 நாடுகள், 1010 நகரங்கள், 63 மொழிகள்</description>
      <description lang="zh">访问rad.io、radio.de和radio.fr上超过7000个国际电台广播的音频插件[CR]现有功能[CR]- 英语、德语和法语支持[CR]- 按地点、类别、主题、国家、城市和语言浏览站点[CR]- 搜索站点[CR]- 115个类别、59个主题、94个国家、1010城市、63种语言</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.radioreference" name="Broadcastify" version="1.1.1" provider-name="xbmchub.com">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Broadcastify</summary>
      <description lang="en">The worlds largest source of Public Safety, Aircraft, Rail and Marine Radio Live Audio Streams</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/official-xbmc-hub-repo/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.ramfm" name="RAM FM Eighties Hit Radio" version="1.0.16" provider-name="spoyser">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">RAM FM Eighties Hits</summary>
      <description lang="en">RAM FM broadcast music within a wide perspective from the years between and around 1975-1995 and some of today's music that would have fit in just fine at the time. RAM FM play all genres of eighties music, from punk to disco, from synth-pop to folk, from rock to easy listening and from new wave to dance. RAM FM play these different genres of eighties music in no special order and without any priority or personal musical preferences involved whatsoever. RAM FM aim to create a realistic musical time image of the eighties. RAM FM never play the same song within 36 hours and never the same artist within 4 hours. Listeners online can request 3 tracks every 30 minutes complying with these musical format and playlist rotation rules.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum>http://www.xunitytalk.com/showthread.php?1480-RELEASE-RAM-FM-Eighties-Hit-Radio</forum>
      <website>http://www.ramfm.org</website>
      <source>http://code.google.com/p/spoyser-repo/source/browse/#git%2Fplugin.audio.ramfm</source>
      <email>seanpoyser at gmail dot com</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.audio.sky.fm"
       name="Sky.fm"
       version="3.0.7"
       provider-name="qualisoft.dk - Tim C. Steinmetz">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GPL 2.0</license>
      <summary lang="en">Sky.fm</summary>
      <description lang="en">
        SKY.FM Radio features a wide variety of free streaming radio channels. Find your favorites among the best of each class - be it New Age, 80s, Smooth Jazz, New Age, Top40, Hip Hop, Oldies, 70s, Reggae, Lounge or many others inside.
      </description>
      <language/>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.1channel" version="2.1.1" name="1Channel" provider-name="Bstrdsmkr">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver"/>
      <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler"/>
      <import addon="script.module.myconnpy"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Browse 1channel.ch</summary>
      <description>This addon is supported at www.XBMCHub.com,lay a wide selection of movies and TV shows from 1channel.ch</description>
      <source>https://raw.github.com/Crazyaddon/MXRepo/master/Repository/repo/</source>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.alaska.hd" name="Alaska HDTV" version="0.0.1" provider-name="divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Alaska HD videos.</summary>
      <description>Travelers and outdoor enthusiasts alike join ﬁfth generation Alaskan Scott Slone as he hikes, boats, climbs and travels throughout some of the most awe-inspiring locations in Alaska.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.aljazeera" name="Al Jazeera" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel)" version="1.9.4">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10" />
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift" version="0.2.0" />
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.4" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="addon.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Watch videos and the live stream from Al Jazeera English.</summary>
      <description lang="en">
        "Drawing on the legacy of the groundbreaking Al Jazeera Arabic channel, Al Jazeera English was launched on November 15, 2006 to more than 80 million households worldwide.[CR][CR] The 24-hour news and current affairs channel is the first international English-language news channel to broadcast across the globe from the Middle East.[CR][CR] Al Jazeera's global footprint continues to grow and now broadcasts to more than 220 million households on six continents in more than 100 countries.[CR][CR] Our channel is broadcast from four strategic broadcast centres: Doha, Kuala Lumpur, London, and Washington DC. Unlike other international channels, we broadcast from our different centres, as the world turns, providing the most comprehensive and contextual news coverage.[CR][CR] Our mission is to provide independent, impartial news for an international audience and to offer a voice to a diversity of perspectives from under-reported regions.[CR][CR] In addition, the channel aims to balance the information flow between the South and the North.[CR][CR] The channel of reference for the Middle East and Africa, Al Jazeera has unique access to some of the world’s most troubled and controversial locations. Our determination and ability to accurately reflect the truth on the ground in regions torn by conflict and poverty has set our content apart."[CR][CR] Source: Al Jazeera
      </description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.beeg.com" name="beeg.com  (Adult) - Powered by XBMCHUB.COM" version="1.0.5" provider-name="MisterX">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="Default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">beeg.com (Adult)</summary>
      <description lang="en">beeg.com (Adult) - Powered by XBMCHUB.COM</description>
      <license>GPL 3.0</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.bestofyoutube_com" name="BestOfYoutube.com" version="2.1.1" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Only the best Youtube clips</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Nur die besten Youtube Videos</summary>
      <language></language>
      <description lang="en">Only the best Youtube clips</description>
      <description lang="de">Nur die besten Youtube Videos</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/AddonScriptorDE/plugin.video.bestofyoutube_com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=132564</forum>
      <email>AddonScriptorDE at yahoo dot de</email>
      <website>http://www.bestofyoutube.com</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.cbsnews_com" name="CBSnews.com" version="2.1.1" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Various news and shows (60 Minutes, 48 Hours, ...)</summary>
      <language>en</language>
      <description lang="en">Various news and shows (60 Minutes, 48 Hours, ...)</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/AddonScriptorDE/plugin.video.cbsnews_com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=136416</forum>
      <email>AddonScriptorDE at yahoo dot de</email>
      <website>http://www.cbsnews.com/videos</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.comicvine"
       name="Comic Vine"
       version="2.1.1"
       provider-name="Whiskey Media">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Comic Vine video plugin</summary>
      <description>Comic Vine is the world's largest comic book website. Watch hundreds of original videos and interviews with comic creators and artists.</description>
      <source>https://github.com/WhiskeyMedia/xbmc</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.crackle2"
       name="Crackle2"
       version="0.0.3"
       provider-name="newatv2user">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="0.9.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Crackle</summary>
      <description lang="en">Shows and Movies from Crackle.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.engineeringtv" name="Engineering TV" provider-name="willforde" version="1.0.2">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcutil" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension library="addon.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Valuable Engineering TV episodes.</summary>
      <description lang="en">Penton Media launched EngineeringTV in 2007 across its design engineering group which includes Electronic Design, Machine Design, Power Electronics Technology, Microwaves &amp; RF, Mobile Dev &amp; Design, Medical Design, Motion System Design, Source ESB and Electronic Design Europe. Since that time it has generated millions of page views and hundreds of thousands of unique visitors.</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
      <email>willforde+xbmc@gmail.com</email>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=178795</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/willforde/plugin.video.engineeringtv</source>
      <website>http://www.engineeringtv.com</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.F.T.V"
       name="F.T.V"
       version="1.2.3a"
       provider-name="kinkin, icon by azad720">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common" version="1.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
               	library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Free to view live streaming</summary>
      <description>Stream Live TV from FilmOn or watch cartoons and movies in the Cartoons and more section. Add movies to library or download.</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.filmontv" name="FilmOn" version="1.4" provider-name="FilmOn.TV Networks Inc">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common" version="1.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">FilmOn</summary>
      <language>en de fr es it ru</language>
      <description lang="en">FilmOn.com is an internet based television provider owned by FilmOn.TV Networks Inc. FilmOn.TV Networks was founded by Alki David in 2006.FilmOn.com subscription packages include access to over 120 streaming TV channels (mostly in English language) in addition to premium FilmOn.com Movie channels and pay-per-view channels. Please visit www.xbmchub.com for assistance with this add-on.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/eleazars-xbmc-add-repository/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.fox.news"
       name="Fox News"
       version="4.0.3"
       provider-name="t1m,divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Fox News</summary>
      <description>
        Watch videos from video.foxnews.com &amp; video.foxbusiness.com.
      </description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=57175</forum>
      <email></email>
      <source>https://github.com/learningit/plugin.video.fox.news</source>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <website>http://video.foxnews.com</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.g4tv"
       name="G4TV"
       version="3.0.2"
       provider-name="stacked">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="1.3.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.buggalo" version="1.1.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">G4TV: The latest in video games - game reviews, trailers, news, cheats, and screenshots.</summary>
      <description lang="en">G4TV is the one destination on television that feeds your addiction for the latest must-have tech gadgets, web culture and video games.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <website>https://code.google.com/p/plugin</website>
      <source>https://github.com/stacked/plugin.video.g4tv</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=43556</forum>
      <email>stacked.xbmc@gmail.com</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.gametrailers" name="GameTrailers" version="1.4" provider-name="Dan Dar3 &lt;dan.dar33@gmail.com&gt;">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python"                 version="1.0"    />
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"  />
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson"    version="2.0.10" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Watch videos from GameTrailers.com</summary>
      <description>Watch videos from GameTrailers.com</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.guardian"
       name="The Guardian"
       version="1.0.2"
       provider-name="Nightflyer">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Video news and features from The Guardian</summary>
      <description>All the latest video content covering news, sport, entertainment and the arts from the Guardian.</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=175703</forum>
      <website>https://github.com/nightflyer73/plugin.video.guardian</website>
      <email></email>
      <source>https://github.com/nightflyer73/plugin.video.guardian</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.hdtrailers_net" name="HD-Trailers.net" version="1.2.2" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://www.hd-trailers.net</website>
      <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.video.hdtrailers_net</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=148400</forum>
      <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <summary lang="ar">مقاطع مرئيه من مصادر مختلفه بجوده عاليه الوضوح</summary>
      <summary lang="be">Trailer and Clips from several sources in HD</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Трейлъри и клипове от няколко източника в HD качество</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Tràiler i Fragments de Vídeo des de diferents fonts en HD</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Trailer og klip fra adskillige kilder i HD</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Trailer und Clips aus verschiedenen Quellen in HD</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Διαφημιστικά και Αποσπάσματα από διάφορες πηγές σε υψηλή ποιότητα (HD)</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Trailer and Clips from several sources in HD</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Trailer y Clips de varias fuentes en HD</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Bandes annonces et Clips provenant de plusieurs sources en HD</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Bandes-annonce et clips vidéos de diverse sources en haute définition</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Trailers e Clips de diferentes fontes en HD</summary>
      <summary lang="he">קדימונים וסרטונים ממספר מקורות באיכות HD</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Najave i video inserti iz nekoliko HD izvora</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Ajánlók és videóklipek számos forrásból HD minőségben</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Trailer e Filmati da svariate fonti in HD</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">다양한 출처의 HD 예고편과 비디오 클립</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Trailers en Clips van verschillende bronnen in HD</summary>
      <summary lang="no">Trailere og snutter fra flere kilder i HD</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Zwiastuny i klipy z kilku źródeł w HD</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Trailers e clipes de várias fontes em HD</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Trailers e Clipes de várias fontes em HD</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Ukážky a klipy z rôznych zdrojov v HD kvalite</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Trailers och klipp från flera olika källor i HD</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">多个来源的高清预告片和电影剪辑</summary>
      <description lang="ar">هذا الملحق يوفر بلوغاً سهلاً للأفلام القصيره ومقاطع اﻷفلام. وبالتحديد يمكنك بلوغها من خلال :[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]اغلب اﻷفلام القصيره متوفره بجوده 480 و 720 و 1080</description>
      <description lang="be">This Plugin provides access to Movie Trailers and Clips. You can download trailers and add movies to CouchPotato. It provides access to Trailers from:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Most of them are available in 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="bg">Добавката предоставя достъп до трейлъри и клипове на филми. Можете да сваляте трейлъри и да добавяте филми в CouchPotato. Предоставя достъп до трейлърите от: [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Повечето са налични в резолюция 480p, 720p и 1080p</description>
      <description lang="ca">Aquest complement permet l'accés a tràilers de pel·lícules i fragments de vídeo. Podeu descarregar tràilers i afegir pel·lícules a CouchPotato. Proporciona accés a Tràilers de:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La majoria d'ells estan disponibles a 480p, 720p i 1080p</description>
      <description lang="da">Denne Addon giver adgang til filmtrailere og klip fra de følgende kilder:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De fleste af dem er tilgængelige i 480p, 720p og 1080p</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieses Plugin bietet Zugriff auf verschiedene Film Trailer und Clips der folgenden Quellen:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Die meisten sind verfügbar in 480p, 720p und 1080p</description>
      <description lang="el">Αυτό το Plugin σας παρέχει πρόσβαση σε Διαφημιστικά και Αποσπάσματα Ταινιών από τις ακόλουθες πηγές:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Τα περισσότερα από αυτά είναι διαθέσιμα σε ανάλυση 480p, 720p και 1080p</description>
      <description lang="en">This Plugin provides access to Movie Trailers and Clips. You can download trailers and add movies to CouchPotato. It provides access to Trailers from:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Most of them are available in 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="es">Este Plugin proporciona acceso a Trailers y Clips de películas. Puede descargar trailers y añadir películas a CouchPotato. Proporciona acceso a Trailer de: [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La mayoría de ellos están disponibles en 480p, 720p y 1080p</description>
      <description lang="fr">Ce plugin donne accès aux Bande-annonces et Clips. Vous pouvez télécharger les bande-annonces et ajouter les films à CouchPotato. Cela donne accès aux Bande-annonces de :[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La plupart sont disponibles en 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">Ce plugiciel permet d'accéder à des bandes-annonces et des clips. Vous pouvez télécharger des bandes-annonces et ajouter des films à Couchpotato. Il donne accès à des bandes-annonces provenant de : [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La plupart sont disponibles en 480p, 720p et 1080p.</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este Engadido fornece de acceso a Trailers e Clips de filmes. Pode baixar trailers e engadir filmes a CouchPotato. Este fornece de acceso a Trailers de:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Moitos deles dispoñíbeis a 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
      <description lang="he">הרחבה זו מספקת גישה לקדימוני סרטים וסרטונים. ביכולתך להוריד קדימונים ולהוסיף סרטים אל CouchPotato. הרחבה זו מאפשרת גישה לקדימונים מ:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]רובם זמינים באיכויות 480p, 720p ו-1080p</description>
      <description lang="hr">Ovaj dodatak omogućuje pristup filmskim najavama i insertima. Možete preuzeti najave i dodati filmove na CouchPotato. Omogućuje pristup najavama iz:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Većina ih je dostupna u 480p, 720p i 1080p kvaliteti.</description>
      <description lang="hu">Ez a modul hozzáférést biztosít filmajánlókhoz és videóklipekhez a következő weboldalakról:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Legtöbbjük elérhető 480p, 720p és 1080p felbontásban is</description>
      <description lang="it">This Plugin fornisce accesso a Trailer di Film e Filmati dalle seguenti fonti::[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]la maggior parte di questi sono disponibili a 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
      <description lang="ko">이 플러그인은 영화 예고편과 클립을 제공합니다. 예고편을 다운로드할 수 있고 CoachPotato에 영화를 추가할 수 있습니다. 아래 사이트의 예고편에 접속할 수 있습니다:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]대부분의 영상은 480p, 720p, 1080p 포맷을 지원합니다.</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze Plugin bied toegang tot Film trailers en Clips. U kunt trailers downloaden en films aan CouchPotato toevoegen. Het bied toegang tot Trailers van:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De meeste zijn beschikbaar in 480p, 720p en 1080p kwaliteit.</description>
      <description lang="no">Dette tillegget gir tilgang til filmtrailere og -snutter. Du kan laste ned trailere og legge filmer til CouchPotato. Den gir tilgang til trailere fra:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]]De fleste er tilgjengelig i 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="pl">Ten Plugin daje dostęp do zwiastunów filmowych i klipów z następujących źródeł:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Większość z nich jest dostępna w 480p, 720p i 1080p</description>
      <description lang="pt">Este plugin permite-lhe ver trailers e clipes de filmes a partir das seguintes fontes:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]A maior parte deles está disponível em 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Este plugin fornece acesso a trailers de filmes e clipes das seguintes fontes:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]A maioria deles está disponível em 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento doplnok poskytuje prístup k ukážkam filmov a ku klipom z týchto zdrojov:&#10; - apple.com&#10; - yahoo.com&#10; - youtube.com&#10; - moviefone.com&#10; - ign.com&#10; - hd-trailers.net&#10; - aol.com&#10;Väčšina z nich je dostupná v rozlíšení 480p, 720p a 1080p.</description>
      <description lang="sv">Detta plugin tillhandahåller trailers hämtade från följande källor:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De flesta är tillgängliga i 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
      <description lang="zh">本插件提供访问预告片和电影剪辑。你可以下载预告片和将电影加入到CouchPotato。支持访问以下来源的预告片：[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]大多为480p、720p和1080p</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.hgtv"
         name="HGTV"
         version="2.0.2"
         provider-name="t1m">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">HGTV Video Addon</summary>
      <description lang="en">Play videos from the HGTV Network</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Feel free to use this script. For information visit the wiki.</disclaimer>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=97018</forum>
      <website>www.hgtv.com</website>
      <email></email>
      <source>https://github.com/learningit/plugin.video.hgtv/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.hollywoodreporter" name="TheHollywoodReporter" version="0.1.0" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift" version="0.2.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.pyamf" version="0.6.1"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language />
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.video.hollywoodreporter</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=139160</forum>
      <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
      <summary lang="ar">فيديو من www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="be">Videos from www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Videos des www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Videoer fra www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Videos von hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Βίντεο από το www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Videos from www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Videos de www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Videos desde www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="fa_IR">ویدیوهایی از www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Vídeos de www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Videók a www.hollywoodreporter.com oldalról</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Video da  www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">www.hollywoodreporter.com의 동영상</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Video iš www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Video's van www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Filmy z www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Vídeos de www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Vídeos de www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Videá z www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Videor från www.hollywoodreporter.com</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">www.hollywoodreporter.com的视频</summary>
      <description lang="ar">المقصد الرئيسي و المصدر الموثوق على نطاق واسع للترفيه, الأخبار, المشاركات. الفيديو و التحليل.</description>
      <description lang="be">The premier destination and most-widely trusted resource for entertainment news, reviews, videos and analysis.</description>
      <description lang="ca">La primera destinació i recurs de confiança amb més acceptació per notícies, reportages, videos i anàlisi d'entreteniment.</description>
      <description lang="da">Den bedste og mest troværdige kilde til nyheder, anmeldelser, videoer og analyser fra og om underholdningsbranchen.</description>
      <description lang="de">Die erste Anlaufstelle und der am meisten vertraute Quelle für Unterhaltung, Neuigkeiten, Tests, Videos und Analysen.</description>
      <description lang="el">Ο κυριότερος προορισμός και η πιο έμπιστη πηγή ψυχαγωγικών ειδήσεων, κριτικών, βίντεο και αναλύσεων.</description>
      <description lang="en">The premier destination and most-widely trusted resource for entertainment news, reviews, videos and analysis.</description>
      <description lang="es">El destino principal y el recurso más fiable de noticias, críticas, videos y análisis del mundo del entretenimiento.</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">La primera y mas confiable fuente para noticias, reviews, videos y análisis del entretenimiento.</description>
      <description lang="fa_IR">مقصد برتر و مطمئن ترین مرجع برای اخبار سرگرمی, نقد و بررسی, فیلم ها و آنالیز.</description>
      <description lang="gl">O principal e maior recurso confiable de novas sobre lecer, opinións, vídeos e análises.</description>
      <description lang="hu">A szórakoztató hírek, visszatekintések, videók és analízisek elsődleges célpontja és legmegbízhatóbb forrása.</description>
      <description lang="it">La risorsa principale per notizie di intrattenimento, recensioni, video e analisi.</description>
      <description lang="ko">엔터테인먼트 뉴스, 리뷰, 비디오와 분석 제공</description>
      <description lang="lt">Geriausia paskirties vieta ir plačiausiai patikimas šaltinis: pramogų naujienos, nuomonės, vaizdo įrašai ir analizės.</description>
      <description lang="nl">De vooraanstaande bestemming en meest betrouwbare bron voor entertainment nieuws, reviews, video's en analyses.</description>
      <description lang="pl">Główne i zarazem najbardziej zaufane źródło powszechnych wiadomości rozrywki, opini, filmów wideo oraz analiz.</description>
      <description lang="pt">Para notícias do mundo do entretenimento, críticas, vídeos e análises, esta é a fonte número um e também a mais fiável.</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">O principal destino e recursos amplamente confiáveis para o entretenimento notícias, análises, vídeos e análise.</description>
      <description lang="sk">Prvý cieľ a najdôveryhodnejší zdroj správ, recenzií, videí a analýz z Hollywoodu.</description>
      <description lang="sv">Den primära destinationen och mest betrodda källan för underhållningsnyheter, granskningar, videor och analyser.</description>
      <description lang="zh">首选和最值得信赖的 娱乐新闻、评论、视频和分析来源</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.howstuffworks_com" name="HowStuffWorks.com" version="2.0.3" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Learn How Everything Works!</summary>
      <language>en</language>
      <description lang="en">Learn How Everything Works!</description>
      <website>http://www.howstuffworks.com</website>
      <source>https://github.com/AddonScriptorDE/plugin.video.howstuffworks_com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=137984</forum>
      <email>AddonScriptorDE at yahoo dot de</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.icefilms"
         name="Icefilms"
         version="1.5.1"
         provider-name="Eldorado (originator: anarchintosh)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
      <import addon="script.module.elementtree" />
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" />
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="2.5.1" />
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.axel.downloader" version="0.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
               library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Stream and download scene releases from the links listed on Icefilms.info</summary>
      <description>
        Visit www.xbmchub.com for support.

        Turns your XBMC into an instant free on-demand media-center. Stream and download to your library pure AVI scene releases, in DVD and HD720p quality. Browse and search the library of over 77,000 videos with metadata and posters. Never experience the frustration of dead video links!
      </description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.ign_com" name="IGN.com" version="2.0.4" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Game and Movie trailers/reviews/news</summary>
      <language>en</language>
      <description lang="en">Game and Movie trailers/reviews/news</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.itunes_podcasts" name="Apple iTunes Podcasts" version="1.1.6" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.feedparser" version="0.5.7"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website></website>
      <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.video.itunes_podcasts</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=143064</forum>
      <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <summary lang="be">Apple iTunes Podcast Browser</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Buscador de Podcast d'Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Udforsk Podcasts fra Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Apple iTunes Podcast Browser</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Περιηγητής Podcast του Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Apple iTunes Podcast Browser</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Explorador de Apple iTunes Podcasts</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Navigateur Apple iTunes Podcast</summary>
      <summary lang="fr_CA">Navigateur de balados d'Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Buscador de Podscasts de Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="he">Apple iTunes Podcast Browser</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Apple iTunes podcast preglednik</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Apple iTunes podcast böngésző</summary>
      <summary lang="id">Peramban Podcast iTunes Apple</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Browser per Podcast di Apple iTunes </summary>
      <summary lang="ko">애플 iTunes 팟캐스트 탐색기</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">Apple iTunes [COLOR=red]Podcast[/COLOR] naršyklė</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Apple itunes Podcast Browser</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Przeglądarka podcastów Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Navegador Apple iTunes Podcast</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Navegador de Podcasts Apple iTunes</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Prehliadač na Apple iTunes Podcast</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Apple iTunes podcast-utforskare</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">Apple iTunes Podcast Tarayıcısı</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">苹果iTunes播客浏览器</summary>
      <description lang="be">This add-on lets you browse and search for thousands of free Podcasts.[CR]NO iTunes Required![CR]It provides both, audio and video podcasts - each devided into over 60 genres. You can also search for specific podcasts by name.[CR]It is also possible to manage a "My Podcasts" list via context-menu.</description>
      <description lang="ca">Aquest complement li permet explorar i buscar milers de podcasts gratuïts.[CR]NO requereix d'iTunes![CR]Proporciona podcasts d'àudio i vídeo - cadascun dividit en més de 60 gèneres. També pot buscar podcasts específics pel seu nom.[CR] També és possible gestionar un llista "Els meus Podcasts" a través del menú contextual.</description>
      <description lang="da">Dette addon lader dig udforske og søge efter tusinder af gratis Podcasts.[CR]Det tilbyder både lyd- og videopodcasts - hver især opdelt i over 60 genrer. Du kan også søge efter specifikke navne på podcasts.[CR]Det er også muligt at håndtere "Mine Podcasts" via kontekstmenuen.</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieses Add-on ermöglicht das durchsuchen von tausenden kostenlosen Podcasts.[CR]Es bieted Video- und Audio-Podcasts - je aufgeteilt auf über 60 Genre. Auch ist es möglich nach Podcasts zu suchen.[CR]Außerdem ist es möglich eine "Meine Podcasts"-Liste über das Kontext-Menu zu verwalten.</description>
      <description lang="el">Αυτό το πρόσθετο σας επιτρέπει να περιηγηθείτε και να αναζητήσετε χιλιάδες δωρεάν Podcast.[CR]Παρέχει podcast βίντεο και ήχου - και τα δύο χωρισμένα σε 60 είδη. Μπορείτε να αναζητήσετε συγκεκριμένα podcast με το όνομα.[CR]Είναι, επίσης, δυνατό να διαχειριστείτε μία λίστα "Podcast μου" μέσω του μενού επιλογών.</description>
      <description lang="en">This add-on lets you browse and search for thousands of free Podcasts.[CR]NO iTunes Required![CR]It provides both, audio and video podcasts - each devided into over 60 genres. You can also search for specific podcasts by name.[CR]It is also possible to manage a "My Podcasts" list via context-menu.</description>
      <description lang="es">Este complemento le permite explorar y buscar entre miles de Podcasts gratuitos.[CR]Proporciona acceso a podcasts de audio y video divididos en más de 60 géneros. Incluso puede buscar podcasts por su nombre.[CR]Incluso es posible manejar sus podcasts mediante la lista "Mis Podacsts" del menú contextual.</description>
      <description lang="fr">Cette extension vous permet de naviguer et trouver des milliers de Podcasts gratuit.[CR]Il existe des podcasts audio et vidéo, divisé en 60 genres différents. Vous pouvez également cherche un podcast par nom.[CR]Il est possible de gérer une liste de "Mes Podcasts" via le menu contextuel.</description>
      <description lang="fr_CA">Cet addiciel vous permet de parcourir et de rechercher des milliers de balados gratuits [CR]iTunes n'est PAS obligatoire![CR]Il fournit à la fois des balados audio et vidéo - divisés en plus de 60 genres. Vous pouvez également rechercher des balados spécifiques par nom.[CR]Il est également possible de gérer une liste « Mes Balados » avec le menu contextuel.</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este complemento permítelle navegar e buscar entre milleiros de Podcasts de balde.[CR]Non é necesario o iTunes.[CR]Fornece tanto de podcasts de son coma de vídeo - cada un dividido entre 60 xéneros. Tamén pode buscar un podcasts concreto polo nome.[CR]Tamén é posible xestionar a listaxe dos "Meus Podcasts" mediante un menú contextual.</description>
      <description lang="he">הרחבה זו מאפשרת לך לעיין ולחפש באלפי פודקאסטים חינמים.[CR]לא נדרש iTunes![CR]היא מציעה גם פודקאסטי אודיו וגם וידאו - המחולקים ליותר מ-60 סגנונות. ניתן לחפש גם פודקאסט מסוים לפי שם.[CR]בנוסף ניתן לנהל רשימת "הפודקאסטים שלי" בעזרת תפריט Context.</description>
      <description lang="hr">Ovaj dodatak vam omogućuje pregledavanje i pretraživanje na tisuće besplatnih Podcasta.[CR]iTunes nije potreban![CR]Pruža vam obadvoje, zvučne i video podcaste - svaki podijeljen u više od 60 žanrova. Isto tako možete pretraživati određene podcaste prema nazivu.[CR]Moguće je upravljanje "Moji podcasti" popisom putem kontekstualnog izbornika.</description>
      <description lang="hu">Ez a kiegészítő lehetővé teszi több ezer ingyenes podcast böngészését és keresését[CR]Hang és videó podcastok is elérhetőek, 60 műfajra osztva. Név szerint is lehetséges a keresés egy adott podcastra.[CR]A helyi menü segítségével kezelheti "saját" podcastjait.</description>
      <description lang="id">Addon ini memungkinkan Anda menjelajahi dan mencari ribuat Podcast gratisan.[CR]Tidak perlu iTunes![CR]Addon menyediakan kedua macam podcast, audio dan video - masing-masing dibagi ke dalam lebih dari 60 tema. Anda juga dapat mencari podcast spesifik menurut namanya.[CR]Anda juga dapat mengelola daftar "Podcast Saya" dari menu konteks.</description>
      <description lang="it">Questo add-on ti permette di sfogliare e cercare centinai di Podcast liberi.[CR]Fornisce sia podcast video che audio - ognuno diviso in 60 generi. puoi cercare podcast specifici per nome.[CR]E' anche possibile gestire la lista: "I miei Podcast" tramite il menù contestuale</description>
      <description lang="ko">이 애드온으로 수천개의 무료 팟캐스트를 탐색하고 검색할 수 있습니다.[CR]각 60개 이상의 장르로 구분된 오디오와 비디오 팟캐스트를 제공합니다. 특정한 팟캐스트를 이름으로 검색할 수 있습니다.[CR]컨텍스트 메뉴를 이용해 "내 팟캐스트" 목록을 관리할 수 있습니다.</description>
      <description lang="lt">Šis priedas leidžia jums naršyti ir ieškoti tūkstančių nemokamai Podcasts [COLOR=red](toliau verčiama kaip - Transliacijos)[/COLOR].[CR]Jis suteikia prieigą prie garso ir vaizdo internetinės medijos failų - kur/katrie kiekvienas suskirstytas į daugiau nei 60 žanrų.Taip pat jūs galite ieškoti konkrečių prenumeruojamų transliacijų pagal pavadinimą.[CR]Taip pat galima valdyti "Mano Transliacijos" sąrašą per kontekstinį meniu.</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze add-on laat je zoeken naar duizenden gratis Podcasts.[CR] GEEN itunes voor vereist![CR] het voorziet zowel in audio en video podcasts - elk uitgesplitst in meer dan 60 genres. je kan ook zoeken voor specifieke podcasts op naam[CR]Het is ook mogelijk  om via het context-menu ''Mijn podcasts'' te beheren.</description>
      <description lang="pl">Wtyczka ta umożliwia ci przeglądanie i szukanie w śród tysięcy darmowych Podcastów.[CR]Posiada zarówno Podcasty audio i video, każde dostępne w ponad 60 gatunkach. Możesz dodatkowo szukać konkretnych Podcastów po nazwie.[CR]Dodatkowo możesz zarządzać listą swoich ulubionych Podcastów poprzez menu kontekstowe.</description>
      <description lang="pt">Este add-on permite-lhe navegar e procurar por milhares de Podcasts grátis.[CR]Oferece podcasts de áudio e vídeo, divididas em mais de 60 géneros. Pode também procurar por nome podcasts específicas.[CR]É também possível gerir uma lista "Minhas Podcasts" através do menu de contexto.</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Este add-on permite que você navegue e pesquise por milhares de Podcasts grátis.[CR]iTunes NÃO é necessário![CR]Fornece tanto podcasts de áudio quanto de vídeo - cada um dividido em 60 gêneros. Você pode também pesquisar por podcasts específicos por nome.[CR]É possível gerenciar uma lista de "Meus Podcasts" através do menu de contexto.</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento doplnok Vám umožní prehliadať a vyhľadávať v tisícoch voľných Podcast-ov.&#10;Poskytuje audio aj video podcast-y - každý rozdelený do viac než 60 žánrov. Môžete zároveň hľadať konkrétny podcast podľa mena.&#10;Zároveň môžete cez kontextové menu spravovať zoznam "Moje Podcast-y".</description>
      <description lang="sv">Detta tillägg låter dig bläddra och söka efter tusentals podcasts.[CR]Det tillhandahåller både ljud- och video-podcasts - Var och en indelad i över 60 genres. Du kan också söka efter specifika podcasts genom namn.[CR]Det är också möjligt att hantera "Mina podcasts"-listan via innehållsmenyn.</description>
      <description lang="zh">本插件可浏览和查找上千个免费播客。[CR]不需要iTunes软件！[CR]支持音频和视频播客 - 均分为60类。你可以按名字搜索播客。[CR]还可以通过上下文菜单管理“我的播客”列表。</description>
      <disclaimer lang="be">NO iTunes required!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="bg">НЕ изисква iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ca">NO requereix d'iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="da">iTunes er ikke nødvendig!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="de">KEIN iTunes benötigt!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="el">Δεν απαιτείται ΚΑΝΕΝΑ iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="en">NO iTunes required!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="es">iTunes no es necesario!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="fi">iTunesia EI vaadita!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="fr">AUCUN iTunes obligatoires!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">iTunes n'est PAS nécessaire!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="gl">Non se require o iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="he">לא נדרש iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="hr">iTunes nije potreban!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="hu">iTunes NEM szükséges!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="it">iTunes non è necessario!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ko">iTunes 필요 없음!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="lt">NO iTunes reikia!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="nl">GEEN iTunes vereist!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pl">Nie wymaga iTunes!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pt">O iTunes não é necessário!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">iTunes NÃO necessário!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="sv">INGEN iTunes krävs!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="tr">iTunes gerekli değil!</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="zh">不需要iTunes软件！</disclaimer>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.joeroganexperience" name="The Joe Rogan Experience" version="2.0.1" provider-name="Lex Toumbourou (lexandstuff) &amp; Paddy Carey (paddycarey)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.0"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.6"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.vimeo" version="3.5.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language></language>
      <summary>Browse and stream videos from The Joe Rogan Experience Podcast</summary>
      <description>Browse and stream videos from The Joe Rogan Experience Podcast</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.movie25"
         name="Mash Up"
         version="1.4.0"
         provider-name="MashUp">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver"  version="0.0.1"/>
      <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common" version="1.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler"  version="1.0.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
               library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Browse Movie25 and many more sources</summary>
      <description lang="en">
        Browse and play a wide selection of movies from the sites like Movie25.com, watchfreeseres, seriesgate, rlsmx, newmyvidelinks etc.
        [COLOR red]Mash Up plugin is coded with Google Analytics which can be disabled in addon settings under General Tab.[/COLOR]
        [COLOR green]Mash Up is Now Officially Ad Free[/COLOR]
      </description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.moviedb" version="2.4.4" name="Cliq!" provider-name="Blazetamer">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver"  version="2.1.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="2.3.1" />
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Cliq! Live Streams Movies/TV</summary>
      <description> "Cliq" Includes iLive Streams, Movies, Tv Shows, Cartoons and Sports from several source websites. Content is updated daily. Download Movies and Shows to your library with a Queue!! Has add-on Wide Favorites! If you want it all Just Cliq!!!</description>
      <disclaimer>The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/blazetamers-repository/17959-%5Brelease%5D-mdb-ultra-video-addon.html</forum>
      <website>http://www.cliqaddon.com/</website>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.newyorktimes" name="New York Times" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel), idleloop" version="1.5">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="1.3.1" />
      <import addon="script.module.requests" version="0.13.2" />
      <import addon="script.module.brightcove" version="1.1.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="addon.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language />
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Watch video from the New York Times.</summary>
      <description>News and opinion video from The NYTimes including breaking news, investigative reporting, national and international coverage. Style and celebrity video.</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
      <source>https://github.com/idleloop-github/xbmc-newyorktimes</source>
      <email>idleloop at yahoo dot com</email>
      <disclaimer>Provided "as is". Original author: web at jonathanbeluch dot com</disclaimer>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.nfl.com"
       name="NFL.com"
       version="0.0.4"
       provider-name="divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Videos from nfl.com.</summary>
      <description>Video highlights from National Football League.com.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/divingmule/plugin.video.nfl.com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=107256</forum>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.on_aol" name="On Aol" version="1.0.1" provider-name="divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="1.3.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Videos form on.aol.com.</summary>
      <description>
        This add-on lets you watch videos from Aol's video portal on.aol.com.
        There is a large variety of content from Aol and their many partners from across the web.
      </description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.projectfreetv"
       name="Project Free TV"
       version="2.2.1"
       provider-name="Eldorado">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" />
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" />
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en"></summary>
      <description lang="en">Visit www.xbmchub.com for support.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.quake.live" name="Quake Live" provider-name="willforde" version="1.0.2">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcutil" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension library="addon.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">QuakeLive, Archived Quake Live Matchs.</summary>
      <description lang="en">QuakeLive.tv's goal is to supply everything in one destination--information on upcoming matches, archives of past matches, tons of great video on demand that shows full-length match replays from the lead shoutcaster's perspetive, an expansive demo collection, and tons of other great, community-building features.</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
      <email>willforde+xbmc@gmail.com</email>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=178799</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/willforde/plugin.video.quake.live</source>
      <website>http://www.quake-live.tv</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.retro_tv" name="retro-tv" version="0.1.1" provider-name="JoJoAction">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">TV of former times</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Fernsehen von früher</summary>
      <language>de</language>
      <description lang="en">retro-tv - TV of former times</description>
      <description lang="de">retro-tv - Fernsehen von früher</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon
    id="plugin.video.retrowaretv"
    version="1.2.0"
    name="Retroware TV"
    provider-name="dethfeet">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.bliptv" version="1.8.3"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
        library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Watch videos from Retroware TV</summary>
      <description>Retroware TV is a classic video games show and website. We will take a look back and discuss those classic games that make Retro Gaming so great. Home to some of the best classic gaming shows on the information superhighway (see, totally retro)</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=111543</forum>
      <website>https://github.com/dethfeet/plugin.video.retrowaretv</website>
      <source>https://github.com/dethfeet/plugin.video.retrowaretv</source>
      <email>dethfeet@qip.ru</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.simply.player" name="Simply Player" version="1.2.1" provider-name="lambda">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="1.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="0.9.1"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="2.9.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup">
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Watch movies and tv shows from simplymovies.net</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Παρακολουθήστε ταινίες και σειρές από το simplymovies.net</summary>
      <description lang="en">Watch movies and tv shows from simplymovies.net</description>
      <description lang="el">Παρακολουθήστε ταινίες και σειρές από το simplymovies.net</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="el">Ο συγγραφέας δεν φιλοξενεί ή διανέμει οποιοδήποτε περιεχόμενο που εμφανίζεται από τo πρόσθετο αυτό. Ο συγγραφέας δεν έχει καμία σχέση με τον πάροχο του περιεχομένου.</disclaimer>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/lambdas-xbmc-repository/</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/lambda81/lambda-xbmc-addons</source>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon
  id="plugin.video.SportsDevil"
  version="1.8.7.8"
  name="SportsDevil"
  provider-name="MaxMustermann">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="0.9.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension
      point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
      library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Play videos of different sports streaming sites</summary>
      <description>Play videos of different sports streaming sites</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.tbh.kidswb"
       name="K[COLOR blue]ids[/COLOR] [COLOR red][B]WB[/B][/COLOR]"
       version="0.0.1"
       provider-name="The[COLOR tan]Highway[/COLOR]">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" version="2.1.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="2.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="aKidsWB.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary></summary>
      <description>Video Addon.  Graphics by TwiztedZero and TheHighway.</description>
      <disclaimer>This Project is developped for XBMC Gotham 13.0 Alpha 6, designed for XBMC Gotham originally, with some mind given to Frodo 12.2/12.3. It gets a slight bit of testing as I use it myself, on a Windows 7 OS with whatever version of XBMC happens to be my main install at that time. Any other OS's / builds of XBMC have not be tested on yet, but do feel free to try and test it out on them. Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing. I take no responsibility for any problems this plugin might in any way, form, shape or size cause. This is project is for a LEARNING EXPERIANCE.</disclaimer>
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/thehighways-xbmc-addons/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/HIGHWAY99/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.tbh.kidswb.dcnation"
       name="K[COLOR blue]ids[/COLOR] [COLOR red][B]WB[/B][/COLOR] - [COLOR green]DC Nation[/COLOR]"
       version="0.0.1"
       provider-name="The[COLOR tan]Highway[/COLOR]">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" version="2.1.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="2.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="aKidsWB_DCNation.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary></summary>
      <description>Video Addon.  Graphics by TwiztedZero and TheHighway.</description>
      <disclaimer>This Project is developped for XBMC Gotham 13.0 Alpha 6, designed for XBMC Gotham originally, with some mind given to Frodo 12.2/12.3. It gets a slight bit of testing as I use it myself, on a Windows 7 OS with whatever version of XBMC happens to be my main install at that time. Any other OS's / builds of XBMC have not be tested on yet, but do feel free to try and test it out on them. Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing. I take no responsibility for any problems this plugin might in any way, form, shape or size cause. This is project is for a LEARNING EXPERIANCE.</disclaimer>
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/thehighways-xbmc-addons/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/HIGHWAY99/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.ted.talks" name="TED Talks" version="4.2.4" provider-name="rwparris2, moreginger">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.elementtree" version="1.2.7"/>
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="0.9.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <!-- There are subtitles on TED in many languages,
    and this plugin is (partially) internationalized in several,
    but it seems better to claim the one we are sure of for now. -->
      <language>en</language>
      <summary lang="en">Watch talks from TED.com, a site dedicated to 'Ideas Worth Spreading'</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Beszédek megtekintése a TED.com-ról</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Veja debates de TED.com, um site dedicado a 'Ideias com Valor'</summary>
      <description lang="en">TED is a small nonprofit devoted to Ideas Worth Spreading. It started out (in 1984) as a conference bringing together people from three worlds: Technology, Entertainment, Design. Since then its scope has become ever broader.</description>
      <description lang="hu">TED egy kicsi non-profit szervezet aminek célpontjában az Ötlet áll amit érdemes megosztani. A webhely kezdete 1984-re nyúlik vissza egy konferenciára ami 3 külön világot hozott össze: Technológia, Szórakozás, Tervezés. Azóta a kör csak bővült.</description>
      <description lang="pt">TED é uma organização sem fins lucrativos dedicada a 'Ideias com Valor'. Foi iniciada em 1984 como uma conferência que pretendia juntar pessoas de três mundos: Tecnologia, Entretenimento e Design. Desde ai tornou-se muito mais abrangente.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=36866</forum>
      <website>https://github.com/moreginger/xbmc-plugin.video.ted.talks</website>
      <source>https://github.com/moreginger/xbmc-plugin.video.ted.talks.git</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.the.daily.show"
         name="The Daily Show"
         version="1.0.9"
         provider-name="Fritzl Inc.">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.requests" version="1.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">The Daily Show with Jon Stewart</summary>
      <description lang="en">Watch full episodes, browse, and search the online archives of Comedy Central's critically acclaimed "fake news" program.</description>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>MIT</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum></forum>
      <email>fritzl-inc@gmx.de</email>
      <source>http://repo.or.cz/r/xbmc-dailyshow.git</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon
      id="plugin.video.the.trailers"
      name="The Trailers"
      version="1.9.5"
      provider-name="Martijn, Sphere">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift" version="0.2.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Watch movie trailers</summary>
      <description lang="en">Watch current movie trailers from[CR]- http://trailers.apple.com[CR]</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Only the most recent 100 or so trailers are listed.</disclaimer>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.theonion_com" name="TheOnion.com" version="2.0.4" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">America's Finest News Source</summary>
      <language>en</language>
      <description lang="en">America's Finest News Source</description>
      <website>http://www.theonion.com</website>
      <source>https://github.com/AddonScriptorDE/plugin.video.theonion_com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=137871</forum>
      <email>AddonScriptorDE at yahoo dot de</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.time_com" name="TIME.com" version="1.0.1" provider-name="AddonScriptorDE">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.pyamf" version="0.6.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Watch videos from the TIME magazine</summary>
      <language>en</language>
      <description lang="en">Watch videos from the TIME magazine</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/AddonScriptorDE/plugin.video.time_com</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=136417</forum>
      <email>AddonScriptorDE at yahoo dot de</email>
      <website>http://www.time.com</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.tmz"
         name="TMZ"
         version="3.0.13"
         provider-name="stacked">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.buggalo" version="1.1.2"/>
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="1.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Celebrity Gossip | Entertainment News | Celebrity News | TMZ.com</summary>
      <description lang="en">Celebrity Gossip and Entertainment News, Covering Celebrity News and Hollywood Rumors. Get All The Latest Gossip at TMZ - Thirty Mile Zone.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <website>https://code.google.com/p/plugin</website>
      <source>https://github.com/stacked/plugin.video.tmz</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=55972</forum>
      <email>stacked.xbmc@gmail.com</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.ultimateguitar"
         name="Ultimate Guitar"
         version="1.0.3"
         provider-name="Kinkin">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
               	library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary>Learn to play guitar!</summary>
      <description>A complete guitar course from Justin Sandercoe, for beginners to advanced players</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.veetle" version="0.2.5" name="Veetle" provider-name="t0mm0">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="1.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point= "xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Browse and stream from veetle.com</summary>
      <description>Enables watching streams on veetle.com that are flash enabled.</description>
      <disclaimer>Does not work for 'HD' streams which require a software download.</disclaimer>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.vevo"
         name="VEVO"
         version="0.7.3"
         provider-name="BlueCop">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.module.demjson" version="1.4"/>
      <import addon="script.module.mechanize" version="0.2.5"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Music Videos from VEVO</summary>
      <description>Music Videos from VEVO</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.vice"
    name="Vice"
    version="1.0.2"
    provider-name="xbmchub.com">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Vice</summary>
      <description lang="en">VICE specializes in exploring uncomfortable truths and going to places we don't belong.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/official-xbmc-hub-repo/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.wsj"
         name="The Wall Street Journal Live"
         version="1.9.4"
         provider-name="t1m">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
              library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">The Wall Street Journal Live</summary>
      <description lang="en">The Wall Street Journal Live XBMC Plugin</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Feel free to use this script. For information visit the wiki.</disclaimer>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=172865</forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source>https://github.com/learningit/plugin.video.wsj</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.xbmchubmaintenance" version="2.1.3"
    name="Maintenance Tool" provider-name="tvaddons.ag">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" />
      <import addon="script.module.metahandler" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Maintenance Tool</summary>
      <description lang="en">Maintenance Tool is your one stop tool for all fixes and information.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://forums.tvaddons.ag/forums/130-MAINTENANCE-TOOL</forum>
      <website>http://www.tvaddons.ag/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.youtube" name="YouTube" provider-name="TheCollective" version="4.4.10">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10" />
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.2" />
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.2" />
      <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">YouTube video byvoegsel</summary>
      <summary lang="be">YouTube video plugin</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Видео добавка за YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Modul videa YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="da">YouTube videoplugin</summary>
      <summary lang="de">YouTube Video Plugin</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Plugin για το YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="en">YouTube video plugin</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Plugin de video de YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Plugin de video de YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Plugin de vídeo de Youtube</summary>
      <summary lang="eu">YouTube bideo gehigarria</summary>
      <summary lang="fa">پلاگین You Tube</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">YouTube-videoliitännäinen</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Extension vidéo YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Extensión de vídeo de YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="he">תוסף וידאו YouTube </summary>
      <summary lang="hu">YouTube video kiegészítő</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Plugin video YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">YouTube ビデオプラグイン</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">YouTube 비디오 플러그인</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">YouTube vaizdo įskiepis</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">YouTube видео додаток</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">YoutTube video plugin</summary>
      <summary lang="no">YouTube video tillegg</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Wtyczka YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Plugin de vídeo YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Plugin de vídeo YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Plugin video YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Дополнение видео YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Zásuvný modul pre video z YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Video vtičnik YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">YouTube videotillägg</summary>
      <summary lang="th">ส่วนเสริมวิดีโอ YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="uk">Відео додаток YouTube</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">YouTube视频插件</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">YouTube 影片外掛</summary>
      <description lang="af">Byvoegsel wat jou toelaat om videos te blaai en speel vanaf almal se gunsteling video werf!</description>
      <description lang="be">Plugin that lets you browse and play videos from everybody's favorite video site!</description>
      <description lang="bg">Добавката Ви позволява да разглеждате и гледате видео клипове от любимия на на всички видео сайт!</description>
      <description lang="cs">Modul, který vám umožní procházet a přehrávat videa z nejoblíbenější stránky s videi.</description>
      <description lang="da">Plugin som lader dig browse og afspille videoer fra alles yndlings videoside!</description>
      <description lang="de">Ein Plugin, welches Ihnen erlaubt Videos von Youtube abzuspielen.</description>
      <description lang="el">Plugin το οποίο σας επιτρέπει να περιηγηθείτε και να δείτε βίντεο από την πιο αγαπητή ιστοσελίδα βίντεο!</description>
      <description lang="en">Plugin that lets you browse and play videos from everybody's favorite video site!</description>
      <description lang="es">Este plugin te permite buscar y reproducir vídeos desde el sitio de vídeos favorito de todos!</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">¡Este plugin te permite buscar y reproducir videos desde el sitio de videos favorito de todos!</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">¡El Plugin que te permite explorar y reproducir vídeos del sitio favorito de todos!</description>
      <description lang="fa">این پلاگین امکان مرور و پخش ویدئو از سایت های ورد علاقه تان را به شما میدهد.</description>
      <description lang="fi">Plugin jolla voi selata ja katsoa videoita kaikkien suosikkivideosivustolta!</description>
      <description lang="fr">Programme permettant parcours et visualisation des chaînes du meilleur site vidéo !</description>
      <description lang="gl">Extensión que permite explorar e reproducir vídeos do sitio favorito de todos!</description>
      <description lang="he">תוסף שמאפשר לך לדפדף ולנגן מתוך אתר הוידאו האהוב על כולם!</description>
      <description lang="hu">A kiegészítő lehetővé teszi mindenkinek, hogy böngésszen, és lejátsszon videókat, mindenki kedvenc videómegosztójáról!</description>
      <description lang="it">Plugin the ti permette di cercare e riprodurre video dal sito di video preferito da tutti!</description>
      <description lang="ja">みんなが大好き、あの有名なサイト上の動画をブラウズ・再生するプラグイン！</description>
      <description lang="ko">YouTube 동영상을 탐색하고 재생할 수 있는 플러그인</description>
      <description lang="lt">Įskiepis, kuris leidžia jums naršyti ir leisti vaizdo įrašus YouTube svetainėje!</description>
      <description lang="mk">Дополнување кое ви овозможува пребарување и пуштање на видеа од омилени видео страни!</description>
      <description lang="nl">Plugin waarmee u kunt bladeren en video's af te spelen vanaf een ieders favoriete video site!</description>
      <description lang="no">Et tillegg som lar deg bla gjennom og spille av videoer fra alles favoritt video nettsted!</description>
      <description lang="pl">Ten plugin pozwala na przeszukiwanie i odtwarzanie wideo z powszechnie lubianej strony!</description>
      <description lang="pt">Plugin que permite procurar e reproduzir vídeos do site favorito de todos!</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Plugin que permite navegar e reproduzir vídeos do site favorito de vídeos de todo mundo!</description>
      <description lang="ro">Plugin ce va permita sa gasiti şi să vizualizaţi videoclipuri de pe site-ul favorit al tuturora.</description>
      <description lang="ru">Данное дополнение позволяет находить и смотреть видео на всеми любимом сайте.</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento zásuvný modul umožňuje prehliadať a prehrávať videá z najobľúbenejšej videostránky na svete!</description>
      <description lang="sl">Vtičnik, ki omogoča predvajanje posnetkov z vaše najljubše video strani!</description>
      <description lang="sv">Tillägget låter dig bläddra och spela videor från allas favoritvideosajt!</description>
      <description lang="th">ส่วนเสริมที่ช่วยให้คุณสามารถเรียกดูและเล่นวิดีโอจากเว็บไซต์วิดีโอที่ทุกคนชื่นชอบ!</description>
      <description lang="zh">让你能浏览和播放最受欢迎的视频网站内容的插件！</description>
      <disclaimer lang="af">Sommige dele van hierdie byvoegsel mag dalk nie wettig wees in jou land van verblyf nie - gaan die plaaslike wette na voor installering.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="be">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="bg">Някои части от добавката може да са незаконни в държавата, в която се намирате - моля, проверете местните закони, преди да я инсталирате.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ca">Algunes parts d'aquest complement poden no ser legals al vostre país de residència - si us plau verificau les lleis locals abans d'instal·lar-lo.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="cs">Některé části tohoto doplňku nemusí být legální ve vašem státě - prosím ověřte vaše zákony před instalací.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="da">Nogle dele af dette add-on er muligvis ikke lovlige i dit hjemland - Kontroller venligst dette ved de lokale myndigheder inden du installerer.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="de">Einige Teile dieses Addons könnten in deinem Land verboten sein - bitte stelle vor der installation sicher, dass du keine Gesetze verletzt.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="el">Κάποια τμήματα αυτού του πρόσθετου ενδέχεται να μην είναι νόμιμα στη χώρα σας - ελέγξετε τη νομοθεσία πριν την εγκατάσταση.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="es">Algunas partes de este addon pueden no ser legales en tu país de residencia - verifica tus leyes locales antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="es_AR">Algunas partes de este add-on pueden no ser legales en tu país de residencia - verifica tus leyes locales antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Algunas partes de este addon pueden no ser legales en tu país de residencia - por favor consulta tus leyes locales antes de instalar</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="fi">Jotkin tämän lisäosan osat eivät ehkä ole laillisia maassasi - tarkista paikalliset lait ennen asentamista.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="fr">Certaines options de cette extension ne sont peut-être pas autorisées dans votre pays - Merci de le vérifier avant son installation.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="gl">Algunhas partes deste engadido poden non ser legais no teu país - por favor verifica as leis locais antes de instalalo.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="he">חלקים מתוסף זה עלולים להיות לא חוקיים במקום מגורייך-אנא בדוק את החוקים החלים עלייך לפני התקנת התוסף.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="hu">A kiegészítő egyes részei lehet, hogy nem legálisak az Ön hazájában - kérjük ellenőrizze a helyi törvényeket a telepítés elött. </disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="it">Alcune parti di questo addon potrebbero non essere legali nel tuo paese di residenza - Ti preghiamo di controllare la tua normativa locale prima di installarlo.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ja">本アドオンの一部は、お住まいの国によっては違法となる可能性があります。インストール前にお住まいの国の法律をご確認ください。</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ko">이 추가기능의 일부분은 사용자의 국가나 거주지역에 따라 합법적이지 않을 수도 있습니다 - 설치하기 전에 관련 법률을 확인하세요.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="lt">Kai kurios šio priedo dalys gali būti Nerodomos/Nepaleidžiamos jūsų Šalyje - prašome patikrinti savo vietinius įstatymus prieš įdiegiant priedą.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="mk">Некои делови од дополнувањето може да не се легални во вашата држава - провери пред да инсталираш.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="nl">
        Sommige onderdelen van deze plugin kunnen illegaal zijn in uw land.
        Raadpleeg de lokale wetgeving voordat u deze plugin installeert.
      </disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="no">Noen deler av dette tillegget kan hende ikke er lovlig i landet du bor i - vennligst sjekk med dine lokale lover før du installerer.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pl">Niektóre części tego dodatku mogą być nielegalne w twoim kraju - przed instalacją sprawdź zgodność ze swoim lokalnym prawem.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pt">Algumas partes deste addon podem não ser legais no seu país de residência - por favor confira as leis regionais antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Algumas partes deste addon podem não ser legais em seu país de residência - por favor, verifique as leis locais antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ro">Unele părți ale acestui addon ar putea fi ilegale în țara ta - verifică legislația locală înainte de a-l instala.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ru">Некоторые элементы этого дополнения могут являться незаконными в вашей стране проживания. Перед установкой ознакомьтесь с местным законодательством.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="sk">Niektoré časti tohto doplnku nemusia byť vo vašej krajine legálne - pred inštaláciou si prosím overte, či je to v súlade s vašim lokálnym právom.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="sl">Deli tega dodatka mogoče niso legalni v kraju vašega bivanja - preverite pred namestitvijo.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="sv">Någon del av detta tillägg kanske är olagligt i ditt land - kontrollera dina lokala lagar innan installation.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="th">บางส่วนจากส่วนขยายนี้อาจไม่ถูกต้องตามกฏหมายในประเทศของคุณ กรุณาตรวจสอบกฏหมายในประเทศของคุณก่อนทำการติดตั้ง</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="zh">这个插件的某些内容可能不符合你所在国家的法律规定 - 请在在安装前确认符合当地法律。</disclaimer>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language />
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="plugin.video.ustvnow" version="0.3.4" name="ustvnow" provider-name="xbmchub.com">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Plays live streams and recordings from ustvnow.com</summary>
      <description>Live streaming US TV. You MUST log in to view streams (see addon settings). You can also play any recordings you have made on ustvnow.com</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <forum>http://www.xbmchub.com/forums/official-xbmc-hub-repo/</forum>
      <website>http://www.xbmchub.com/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.common.plugin.cache" name="Common plugin cache" provider-name="TheCollective" version="2.5.5">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.service" start="startup">
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Common caching api for xbmc plugins.</summary>
    </extension>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.funnyordie"
       name="Funny Or Die"
       version="0.0.3"
       provider-name="divingmule">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>funnyordie.com Videos</summary>
      <description>
        Funny Or Die is a comedy website that combines user-generated content with original, exclusive content.[CR]
        The site is a place where celebrities, established and up-and-coming comedians and regular users can all put up stuff they think is funny.
      </description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>en</language>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <source>https://github.com/divingmule/script.funnyordie</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=174829</forum>
      <website>http://www.funnyordie.com</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.addon.common"
         name="Common addon methods"
         version="2.0.0"
         provider-name="Eldorado (original: t0mm0)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
      <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.axel.downloader"
         name="Axel Downloader"
         version="0.2.0"
         provider-name="Eldorado">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="controlpanel.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.service" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Multi-connection/threaded Downloader</summary>
      <description lang="en">Download a file using multiple connections to achieve the highest speed.</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup"
         name="BeautifulSoup"
         version="3.2.1"
         provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python"
          version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>HTML/XML parser for quick-turnaround applications like screen-scraping</summary>
      <description>Beautiful Soup parses arbitrarily invalid SGML and provides a variety of methods and Pythonic idioms for iterating and searching the parse tree.</description>
      <license>BSD</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup4"
         name="BeautifulSoup4"
         version="4.3.2"
         provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python"
          version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>HTML/XML parser for quick-turnaround applications like screen-scraping</summary>
      <description>Beautiful Soup parses arbitrarily invalid SGML and provides a variety of methods and Pythonic idioms for iterating and searching the parse tree.</description>
      <license>BSD</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://www.crummy.com/software/BeautifulSoup/</website>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.brightcove" name="Brightcove" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel)" version="1.1.1">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.buggalo" name="Buggalo Exception Collector" version="1.1.5" provider-name="twinther">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="be">Automatic exception collector</summary>
      <summary lang="da">Automatisk indsamling af fejl</summary>
      <summary lang="de">Automatische Fehlerberichterstattung</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Αυτόματος συλλέκτης εξαιρέσεων</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Automatic exception collector</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Capturador automático de excepciones</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Recogedor de excepcion automatica</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Collecteur automatique d'exceptions</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Recolector automático de excepcións</summary>
      <summary lang="he">אוסף חריגות אוטומטי</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">Automatikus kivételgyűjtő</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Raccoglitore automatico di eccezioni</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Automatische uitzondering verzamelaar</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Automatyczny kolekcjoner wyjątków.</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Recolector automático de excepções</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">Coletor exceção automática</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">Automatický zberateľ výnimiek</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Automatisk undantagsfelsinsamlare</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">异常自动收集器</summary>
      <description lang="be">This module can collect various information about an exception and the users system such as XBMC and Python versions, etc. and submit it to a url.</description>
      <description lang="da">Dette modul kan indsamle forskellige informationer om en fejl og brugerens system såsom XBMC- og Pythonversioner osv. og sende det til en webadresse.</description>
      <description lang="de">Dieses Modul kann diverse Informationen über einen Programm-Fehler sowie die Umgebung (XBMC- und Python-Versionen) sammeln und zu einer URL senden.</description>
      <description lang="el">Αυτό το εργαλείο μπορεί να συλλέγει διάφορες πληροφορίες σχετικά με μία εξαίρεση καθώς και τις XBMC και Python εκδόσεις του συστήματος του χρήστη, κτλ., και να τις υποβάλλει σε μία διεύθυνση url.</description>
      <description lang="en">This module can collect various information about an exception and the users system such as XBMC and Python versions, etc. and submit it to a url.</description>
      <description lang="es">Este módulo recopila información acerca de una excepción y el sistema de los usuarios (por ejemplo las versiones de XBMC y Python, etc) y la envía a una URL.</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">Este modulo puede recoger varia informacionacerca de una excepcion y usuarios del sistema como XBMC y versiones Python, etc. y enviarlo a una url.</description>
      <description lang="fr">Ce module peut collecter différentes informations sur une exception et le système comme les versions d'XBMC et de Python, etc. et les soumettre sur une URL.</description>
      <description lang="gl">Este módulo pode recoller diversa información sobre unha excepción e o sistema dos usuarios , como o XBMC e as versións de Python, etc, e envialo a un url.</description>
      <description lang="he">מודול זה יכול לאסוף מידע מגוון על חריגה ומערכת המשתמש כמו גרסאות XBMC, פייתון וכדו'. ולשלוח זאת לכתובת.</description>
      <description lang="hu">Ez a modul információkat szolgáltat a kiváltott kivételekről és a felhasználó rendszeréről(, mint pl. az XBMC vagy Phyton verzió) és egy URL-be helyezi.</description>
      <description lang="it">Questo modulo può raccogliere varie informazioni circa un'eccezione ed il i sistemi degli utenti come le versioni di XBMC e di Pyton, ecc.... ed inviarle ad un url</description>
      <description lang="nl">Deze module kan diverse informatie verzamelen over uitzonderingen en van het systeem van de gebruiker zoals XBMC en Python versie, enz. en deze versturen naar een URL.</description>
      <description lang="pl">Modół ten potrafi zbierać różne informacje o wyjątkach, użytkownikach systemów takich jak XBMC oraz Python etc, i przesłać je na podany adres url.</description>
      <description lang="pt">Este módulo pode recolher diversas informações sobre uma excepção  e sobre o sistema dos utilizadores, como o XBMC e as versões de Python, etc, e submetê-las para uma url.</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Este módulo pode coletar diversas informações sobre uma exceção no sistema dos usuários, tais como o XBMC e versões de Python, etc, e submetê-lo para uma url</description>
      <description lang="sk">Tento doplnok môže zbierať rôzne informácie o vzniknutých výnimkách, užívateľskom systéme ako je XBMC, o verzii Python a inom a odoslať ich na URL.</description>
      <description lang="sv">Den här modulen kan samla in diverse information om undantagsfel och användarens system, såsom XBMC och Python-versioner, etc. och skicka in det till en url.</description>
      <description lang="zh">此组件可以收集一个异常或用户系统相关的多方面信息如XBMC和Python的版本等。并将此信息发送到一个网址</description>
      <license>GPLv2</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <email>tommy@winther.nu</email>
      <website>http://tommy.winther.nu</website>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=121925</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/twinther/script.module.buggalo</source>
      <language></language>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.demjson"
         name="demjson"
         version="1.4"
         provider-name="deron.meranda.us">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.dmd-czech.common" name="dmd-czech common python modules" version="1.5.3" provider-name="Jiri Vyhnalek">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>dmd-czech plugins common python modules</summary>
      <description>Common python modules pack that is used by dmd-czech plugins</description>
      <license>GNU GPL</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.elementtree"
       name="Elementtree XML parser"
       version="1.2.8"
       provider-name="http://effbot.org/zone/element-index.htm">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.feedparser" name="feedparser" version="5.1.3" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <summary lang="en">Python helper module</summary>
      <description lang="en">feedparser is a Python library that parses feeds in all known formats, including Atom, RSS, and RDF. It runs on Python 2.4 all the way up to 3.2.</description>
      <license>MIT</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>https://code.google.com/p/feedparser/</website>
      <source>https://code.google.com/p/feedparser/source/browse/</source>
      <forum></forum>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.mechanize"
	name="Mechanize"
	version="0.2.6"
	provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python"
          version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
         library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Stateful programmatic web browsing in Python, after Andy Lester’s Perl module WWW::Mechanize.</summary>
      <description lang="en">packed for xbmc from https://github.com/jjlee/mechanize</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">packed for xbmc from https://github.com/jjlee/mechanize</disclaimer>
      <forum></forum>
      <website>http://wwwsearch.sourceforge.net/mechanize/</website>
      <license>BSD</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <source>https://github.com/jjlee/mechanize</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.metahandler"
     name="metahandler"
     version="2.9.0"
     provider-name="Eldorado">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.6"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Music videos for addons and stores them in a local SQLITE database</summary>
      <description lang="en">Queries, stores, and returns metadata for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos. [CR]Sources:[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]www.imdb.com</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
      <language></language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website></website>
      <email></email>
      <source></source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.myconnpy"
       name="MySQL Connector/Python"
       version="1.1.7"
       provider-name="MySQL">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python</summary>
      <description lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python is implementing the MySQL Client/Server protocol completely in Python. This means you don't have to compile anything or MySQL (client library) doesn't even have to be installed on the machine.</description>
      <license>GPLv2</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://dev.mysql.com/doc/connector-python/en/index.html</website>
      <source>http://dev.mysql.com/downloads/connector/python/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.parsedom" name="Parsedom for xbmc plugins" provider-name="TheCollective" version="2.5.2">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Parsedom for xbmc plugins.</summary>
    </extension>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <license>GPLv3</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <email></email>
      <website></website>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=116498</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/HenrikDK/xbmc-common-plugin-functions</source>
      <language></language>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.pyamf"
       name="PyAMF"
       version="0.6.2"
       provider-name="Mark Honeychurch (markhoney)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python"
          version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>PyAMF provides Action Message Format (AMF) support for Python that is compatible with the Adobe Flash Player.</summary>
      <description>
        The Adobe Integrated Runtime and Adobe Flash Player use AMF to communicate between an application and a remote server. AMF encodes remote procedure calls (RPC) into a compact binary representation that can be transferred over HTTP/HTTPS or the RTMP/RTMPS protocol. Objects and data values are serialized into this binary format, which increases performance, allowing applications to load data up to 10 times faster than with text-based formats such as XML or SOAP.
        AMF3, the default serialization for ActionScript 3.0, provides various advantages over AMF0, which is used for ActionScript 1.0 and 2.0. AMF3 sends data over the network more efficiently than AMF0. AMF3 supports sending int and uint objects as integers and supports data types that are available only in ActionScript 3.0, such as ByteArray, ArrayCollection, ObjectProxy and IExternalizable.
      </description>
      <license>MIT</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <source>http://www.pyamf.org/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.pytz" name="pytz" version="2014.2" provider-name="Stuart Bishop, Paul Backhouse">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">World Timezone Definitions for Python.</summary>
      <description lang="en">pytz brings the Olson tz database into Python. This library allows accurate and cross platform timezone calculations using Python 2.4 or higher. It also solves the issue of ambiguous times at the end of daylight saving time, which you can read more about in the Python Library Reference (datetime.tzinfo).</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language></language>
      <license>MIT</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website>https://pypi.python.org/pypi/pytz/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/powlo/script.module.pytz</source>
      <email></email>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Use at your own risk. The authors accept no liability. May cause permanent and/or catastrophic damage. Side effects include, but are not limited to loss of memory, seizures, sudden fits of rage, sudden fits of melancholy, inability to recall prominent capital cities, lack of respect for authority, fear of cats, temporary and/or permanent black outs. Avoid inhalation. Use in a well ventilated space. Keep away from small children.</disclaimer>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.requests"
       name="requests"
       version="2.3.0"
       provider-name="kennethreitz, beenje">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Python HTTP for Humans</summary>
      <description>Packed for XBMC from https://github.com/kennethreitz/requests</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language></language>
      <license>Apache2</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website>http://python-requests.org</website>
      <source>https://github.com/beenje/script.module.requests</source>
      <email>beenje AT gmail.com</email>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.simple.downloader" name="Simple Downloader for xbmc plugins" provider-name="TheCollective" version="1.9.4">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.service" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Simple downloader for xbmc plugins.</summary>
    </extension>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.simplejson"
       name="simplejson"
       version="3.3.0"
       provider-name="Martijn">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
               library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language></language>
      <summary lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</summary>
      <description lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Code taken from https://pypi.python.org/pypi/simplejson/</disclaimer>
      <license>MIT License, Academic Free License v. 2.1</license>
      <website>https://pypi.python.org/pypi/simplejson/</website>
      <source>https://pypi.python.org/pypi/simplejson/</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.t0mm0.common"
         name="t0mm0's common stuff"
         version="2.1.1"
         provider-name="t0mm0">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
      <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.TheYid.common"
         name="TheYid's common stuff"
         version="0.1.2"
         provider-name="TheYid">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
      <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.urlresolver"
     name="URLResolver"
     version="2.10.0"
     provider-name="Eldorado">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
      <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common" version="2.0.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
      <description lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.xbmcswift" name="xbmcswift" version="0.2.2" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel)">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <source>https://github.com/jbeluch/xbmcswift</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.xbmcswift2" name="xbmcswift2" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel)" version="2.4.0">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language />
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.xbmcutil" name="XBMC Utility Pack" provider-name="willforde" version="2.1.0">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language>en</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <summary lang="en">XBMC Utility Pack</summary>
      <description lang="en">Control Pack for Class Integration</description>
      <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
      <email>willforde+xbmc@gmail.com</email>
      <source>https://github.com/willforde/script.module.xbmcutil</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.module.xmltodict" name="xmltodict" version="0.9.0" provider-name="martinblech">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <language></language>
      <summary lang="en">Python helper module</summary>
      <description lang="en">xmltodict is a Python module that makes working with XML feel like you are working with JSON, as in this "spec".[CR]</description>
      <license>MIT</license>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>https://github.com/martinblech/xmltodict</website>
      <source>https://github.com/martinblech/xmltodict</source>
      <forum></forum>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.xbmc.pandorajson"
       name="Pandora Json"
       version="1.3.01"
       provider-name="spbogie, newatv2user">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
               library="default.py">
      <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Pandora Radio</summary>
      <description lang="en">Pandora Internet Radio for XBMC.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.xbmc.subtitles"
         name="XBMC Subtitles"
         version="3.9.18"
         provider-name="amet, mr_blobby">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
      <import addon="script.module.mechanize" version="0.2.5"/>
      <import addon="script.module.requests" version="1.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.subtitles"
               library="default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="af">XBMC Subtitels</summary>
      <summary lang="ar">ترجمات XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="be">XBMC Subtitles</summary>
      <summary lang="bg">Субтитри за XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="ca">Subtítols XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="cs">Titulky XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="da">XBMC Undertekster</summary>
      <summary lang="de">XBMC Untertitel</summary>
      <summary lang="el">Υπότιτλοι XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="en">XBMC Subtitles</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Subtítulos XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="es_AR">Subtítulos XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="es_MX">Subtítulos XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="et">XBMC Subtiitrid</summary>
      <summary lang="eu">XBMC azpitituluak</summary>
      <summary lang="fi">XBMC-tekstitykset</summary>
      <summary lang="fr">Sous-titres XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="gl">Subtítulos de XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="he">XBMC Subtitles</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">XBMC Podnaslov</summary>
      <summary lang="hu">XBMC feliratok</summary>
      <summary lang="it">Sottotitoli XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="ja">XBMC Subtitles</summary>
      <summary lang="ko">XBMC 자막</summary>
      <summary lang="lt">XBMC subtitrai</summary>
      <summary lang="mk">XBMC Преводи</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">XBMC Ondertitels</summary>
      <summary lang="no">XBMC undertekster</summary>
      <summary lang="pl">Napisy XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="pt">Legendas XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="pt_BR">XBMC Legendas</summary>
      <summary lang="ro">Subtitrări XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="ru">Субтитры XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="se">XBMC Undertexter</summary>
      <summary lang="sk">XBMC Titulky</summary>
      <summary lang="sl">Podnapisi XBMC</summary>
      <summary lang="sr">XBMC Преводи</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">XBMC Undertexter</summary>
      <summary lang="th">XBMC คำบรรยาย</summary>
      <summary lang="tr">XBMC Altyazılar</summary>
      <summary lang="zh">XBMC 字幕</summary>
      <summary lang="zh_TW">XBMC 字幕</summary>
      <description lang="af">Soek en laai subtitels af van verskeie verskaffers. Subtitel knoppie op OSD moet geaktiveer wees en pad gestel na XBMC Subtitels onder Stelsel-&gt; Oortreksel-&gt; Byvoegsel Skripte</description>
      <description lang="be">Search and download subtitles from multipe providers.Subtitle button on OSD needs to be activated and path set to XBMC Subtitles under System-&gt; Skin-&gt; Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="bg">Търси и сваля субтитри от многобройни източници. Трябват ли ви субтитри на български език пробвайте OpenSubtitles.org. Ползващите Eden могат да вкл/изкл бутона за субтитрите от Настройки &gt; Облик &gt; Добавка &gt; Видео OSD</description>
      <description lang="ca">Busca i descarrega subtítols a múltiples proveïdors. El botó de subtítulos al OSD s'ha d'activar a Sistema-&gt;Skin-&gt;Scripts d'Addon, establint la ruta a XBMC Subtitles</description>
      <description lang="cs">Hledejte a stahujte titulky od více poskytovatelů. Je třeba aktivovat tlačítko Titulky na OSD a nastavit cestu k titulkům pro XBMC v sekci Systém -&gt; Vzhled -&gt; Skripty doplňků</description>
      <description lang="da">Søg efter og download undertekster fra en række udbydere. Undertekst-knappen på OSD skal aktiveres og stien sættes til XBMC Subtitles under System-&gt; Skin -&gt; Add-on Scripts</description>
      <description lang="de">Suche und lade Untertitel von verschiedenen Anbietern. </description>
      <description lang="el">Αναζήτηση και λήψη υποτίτλων από διάφορους παρόχους. Το πλήκτρο υποτίτλων πρέπει να είναι ενεργό στο OSD και να έχει οριστεί η διαδρομή στους υπότιτλους XBMC στο Σύστημα -&gt; Κέλυφος -&gt; Πρόσθετα Script</description>
      <description lang="en">Search and download subtitles from multipe providers.Subtitle button on OSD needs to be activated and path set to XBMC Subtitles under System-&gt; Skin-&gt; Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="es">Búsqueda y descarga de subtítulos desde múltiples proveedores.Se necesita activar el botón de subtitulos en OSD y establecer a XBMC subtítulos en Sistema-&gt;Skin-&gt;Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="es_AR">Buscar y descargar los subtítulos desde múltiples proveedores.Se necesita activar el botón de subtítulos en OSD y establecer a XBMC subtítulos en Sistema-&gt;Skin-&gt;Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="es_MX">Búsqueda y descarga de subtítulos de distintos proveedores. El botón de subtítulos en el OSD requiere ser activado con la ruta definida hacia XBMC Subtitles en Systema-&gt;Skin-&gt;Scripts de Addons</description>
      <description lang="et">Otsi ja lae alla subtiitreid erinevatelt pakkujatelt.Subtiitrite nupp OSD juures peab olema aktiveeritud ja teekonnaks peab olema seatud XBMC Subtiitrid  Süsteemid-&gt; Rüü-&gt; Lisade kood</description>
      <description lang="fi">Hae ja lataa tekstityksiä monelta tarjoajalta. Tekstitysnappi pitää aktivoida ja hakemistopolku pitää asettaa XBMC-tekstityksiin Järjestelmä -&gt; Skin/Kuosi -&gt; Lisäosaskriptit</description>
      <description lang="fr">Recherche et téléchargement de sous-titres depuis différentes sources. Activer le bouton de sous-titre dans le menu à l'écran et définir le chemin de sous-titres dans System-&gt;Thème-&gt;Scripts d'extension</description>
      <description lang="gl">Busca e descarga subtítulos dende varios provedores. O botón dos subtítuos on OSD ten de estar activado e o camino estabelecido en Subtítulos XBMC baixo Sistema-&gt; Tema-&gt; Scripts dos Engadidos</description>
      <description lang="he">חפש והורד כתוביות ממספר ספקים. כפתור הכתוביות בתפריט ה-OSD צריך להיות פעיל והנתיב צריך היות מוגדר לכתוביות XBMC תחת מערכת -&gt; מעטפת -&gt; הרחבות סקריפטים</description>
      <description lang="hr">Pretraživanje i preuzimanje titlova od više  providera.Subtitle gumb na OSD-u potreban je da se aktivira put u postavkama na XBMC Titlovi pod System-&gt; Skin-&gt; Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="hu">Feliratok keresése és letöltése több internetes szolgáltatótól. A feliratok gombot az OSD-n aktiválni kell az elérési út beállításával a Beállítások-&gt;Megjelenítés-&gt;Felszín-&gt;Kiegészítő parancsikonok menüpont alatt</description>
      <description lang="it">Cerca e scarica i sottotitoli da più fornitori. Il pulsante Sottotitoli sull'OSD deve essere attivo e il percorso impostato su Sottotitoli XBMC sotto Sistema -&gt; Skin -&gt; Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="ko">다양한 사이트에서 자막을 찾고 다운로드합니다. OSD에서 자막 버튼을 사용하려면 '시스템 &gt; 스킨 &gt; 자막 추가기능' 에서 'XBMC Subtitles'를 선택하여 활성화하여야 합니다.</description>
      <description lang="lt">Ieškoti ir atsisiųsti subtitrus iš Multipe teikėjų. Paantraštės mygtukas OSD turi būti aktyvuotas. Nustatytas kelias iki XBMC Subtitrai -&gt; Sistema -&gt; Teminė išvaizda/Tema -&gt; Addon Skriptai</description>
      <description lang="mk">Барај и превземи преводи од повеќе добавувачи. Копчето за преводи на OSD треба да е активирано и патеката да биде подесена на XBMC Преводи при Систем-&gt; Маска-&gt; Скрипти на додаток</description>
      <description lang="nl">Zoek en download ondertitels van meerdere aanbieders. De ondertitel knop in het OSD scherm moet zijn geactiveerd met het pad naar XBMC Subtitles via Systeem-&gt; Skin-&gt; Addon Scripts.</description>
      <description lang="pl">Wyszukaj i pobierz napisy równoczesnie z wielu źródeł. Przycisk napisów w Menu Ekranowym powinien zostać aktywowany w opcjach XBMC. Ścieżka: System-&gt; Skóra-&gt; Skrypty Addon-&gt; XBMC Subtitles</description>
      <description lang="pt">Procure e transfira legendas de vários fornecedores. O botão das legendas deve ser adicionado no visor e a localização definida em Sistema-&gt; Tema-&gt; Addons</description>
      <description lang="pt_BR">Procure e efetue download de legendas de múltiplos provedores. Botão de Legendas na tela OSD precisa ser ativado manualmente e o caminho deve estar definido para o XBMC Legendas em Sistema-&gt; Skin-&gt; Scripts de Addons. </description>
      <description lang="ro">Caută şi descarcă subtitrari folosind servicii multiple. Butonul de subtitrări in OSD trebuie să fie activat şi calea trebuie să fie setată in XBMC-&gt; Costume -&gt; Scripturi supliment</description>
      <description lang="ru">Поиск и загрузка субтитров со множества сайтов. Необходимо включить кнопку субтитров в OSD и выбрать дополнение субтитров в настройках обложки.</description>
      <description lang="se">Sök och ladda ner undertexter från flera källor. Undertextknappen i OSD'n behöver aktiveras och sökvägen anges till XBMC Undertexter i Inställningar -&gt; Skal -&gt; Tillägg genvägar</description>
      <description lang="sk">Hľadajte a preberajte titulky od viacerých poskytovateľov. Je potrebné aktivovať tlačidlo Titulky na OSD obrazovke a nastaviť cestu k adresáru pre XBMC Titulky v ponuke Systém-&gt; Vzhľad-&gt; Skripty doplnkov</description>
      <description lang="sl">Poiščite in prenesite podnapise različnih ponudnikov. Gumb za podnapise na OSD mora biti vključen in nastavljen na dodatek v nastavitvah preobleke.</description>
      <description lang="sr">Претражи и скини преводе од многобројних провајдера. Дугме за преводе на OSD треба да се активира и изабере XBMC Subtitles у Систем-&gt; Маска-&gt; Скрипт додаци</description>
      <description lang="sv">Sök och ladda ner undertexter från flera källor. Undertextknappen på OSB behöver vara aktiverad och sökvägen till XBMC Undertexter angiven i System -&gt; Skal -&gt; Tillägg</description>
      <description lang="th">ค้นหาและดาวน์โหลดคำบรรยายจากผู้ให้บริการหลายแหล่ง ปุ่มคำบรรยายที่อยู่ในการแสดงผลหน้าจอจำเป็นต้องเปิดใช้งานและตั้งค่าในส่วนของการตั้งค่าคำบรรยายใน System-&gt; Skin-&gt; Addon Scripts</description>
      <description lang="zh">从多个服务提供者搜索并下载字幕。需要激活视频OSD菜单中的字幕按钮，并将字幕扩展功能设置为XBMC字幕。设置方法：系统设置-&gt;皮肤-&gt;扩展功能</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website></website>
      <source>https://github.com/amet/script.xbmc.subtitles</source>
      <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=126495</forum>
      <email></email>
    </extension>
  </addon>

</addons>
